But as soon as you start playing games, I start playing games, and at any moment, I can hit that yay button.
Now my words and my rules, I just enforce them all right?
I'm there at the first day.
Jesus is the way and the life and the king of Israel.
We just leave with love.
Now my words and my rules, I just enforce them all right?
God is using me, He's breaking me down, removing all of the, you know, riches person, all of this so I can serve Him.
I think I think they've been extremely unfair to you.
People that are scrambling trying to protect their ever shrinking share of what they have are foolish, it's all going, it's all going away.
This country is being ripped apart and raped and looted.
We're being slowly poisoned and in some cases quickly murdered and assassinated.
And we're killing ourselves every day inadvertently with the kinds of things that we eat and breathe and drink and see.
People have got to start to radically begin to obey their conscience and tell the truth and do the right thing.
And people have got to start to get courageous and this is the time for everybody to turn and look to God and to pray and to ask for strength and to ask for wisdom to get through this time and to transform and sanctify this country.
The alternative is that there will be no country.
Is it really only as big as low gas prices? Is it really only so big as bringing inflation and gas prices and the corporate tax rate back down?
Is that about waiting for someone to come in and change the policy and make it better?
It's a personal decision that we all have to make to become soldiers of Christ.
Oh, wow, wow.
What's up, look at the time.
The broken plot is right again.
Your ability informed.
I am the loser.
What I want you.
Hello, hello, hello, hello.
Hello.
Got faces to beat.
Good evening, everybody.
You're watching America First.
My name is Nicholas J. Flimchester.
We have a great show for you tonight.
everybody
You got that
No one's allowed to say that the blind is quintessential part of this, that the blind
of our people is something that is essential.
But we are different, that America was different because we are different.
Palantir is an AI data analytics company that uses artificial intelligence to look at
vast amounts of data and create insights.
If the government has an amount of data which is kind of unimaginable, if you've got
every phone call, every email, every transaction, every photograph of a license plate on the
highway satellite data, it's too much data for a bureaucracy to sift through.
Palantir comes in and interprets the data using algorithms, using artificial intelligence,
using software to make vast amounts of data usable.
That's what they are.
And so many of the people that worked with Elon that came into the government through
Doge worked with Palantir.
Now that Doge is finished, Palantir seems to be just getting started.
How much everybody can I just say, are you trusty?
How much everybody can I just say?
And the reason why is because it's not good to share a big business, it's not good to
share a big business, it's not good to share a big business, it's not good to share a big business
It's not good to share a big business, it's not good to share a big business, it's not good to share a big business
It's not good to share a big business, it's not good to share a big business
It's not good to share a big business, it's not good to share a big business, can you share a big business
Thank you so much everybody, can I just say, are you trusty?
When I get home, I want you, hello, hello, hello, hello, I got places to be here
Good evening everybody, you're watching America First, my name is Nicholas J. Fuentes, we have a great show for you tonight
Thank you so much everybody, thank you so much everybody, can I just say, are you trusty?
My love has got no money. He's got his strawberries. My love has got no power. He's got his strong beliefs. My love has got no fame. He's got his strawberries. My love has got no money. He's got his strong beliefs.
One more and more. People just want more and more. Freedom and love. What he's looking for. One more and more. People just want more and more. Freedom and love.
What he's looking for. Freedom and love. What he's looking for. Freedom and love.
If we don't have freedom on the internet in the age of AI, we are going to be mind-raped every day forever.
Think about anything you've ever said or done in the vicinity of your phone's camera or microphone. Everything you've ever put into your phone.
And even things that are not necessarily so scandalous, but even things like your favorite restaurants, your geo location because your phone also has a GPS. They know where you are at all times. They know where you go and when. They know what you buy. They have access to your bank account.
AI will literally know everything about you. Everyone you know, your relationship to them, your taste, your preferences, your habits, your whereabouts, your routines, your schedule, when you are sleep.
They know how much REM sleep you're getting. They know you're resting heart rate. They know how many calories you consume.
Think about the ways that they manipulate you. You have a computer in your refrigerator, computer in your car, computer in your home security system, computer in your everything, computer in your clothes, your watch, your glasses, your VR headset, your alarm clock.
You have a smart home, economy of things. It's like total rate of everybody by the system forever.
My life is like a first person video game. You know, this is like, this is my primary. This is me like walking down the hall. This is my primary weapon.
Press circle to interact. Press circle to interact with this item.
At the end of the day, here's a question. Is it worth it to save the country? Does the country matter? Is it worth it to preserve our civilization? Is it worth it to preserve our religion?
May it be bigger than that? Is the truth worth it? What is the truth worth to you? What is telling the truth worth to you? Is it worth something? Nothing? What are you willing to give to tell the truth?
All you need is Jesus. All you need is prayer. These material appetites, they will never be satisfied. And even if they are, it will never be an adequate substitute for communion with our Holy Father with somebody with the author of the world.
And every mother and father understands the love for a child. And that is how we were made, we were designed that way.
Because through that experience, we could understand by analogy God's love for us. It says in Revelation that God will wipe away every tear.
And that's like to mean. It makes you want to cry when I read that.
People experience these things in their lives. We've all been there. You feel like the whole world is against you, the walls are closing in.
And you read something like that that says that God, like our Father, our Creator, is going to wipe your tears off your face.
Christianity is love. Our God is love.
A
Jesus Christ was our past. Jesus Christ is our present now. And Jesus Christ is our future after we die on it.
We want this century to be the most Christian century in the history of plan.
Jesus Christ is our future.
I'm not supposed to be here tonight.
I'm supposed to be here.
Good evening everybody.
You're watching America First.
My name is Nicholas J. Flinches.
We have a great show for you tonight.
I'm not supposed to be here tonight.
I'm supposed to be here tonight.
Pleasure to have guests in charge!
Pleasure to have guests in charge.
I'm supposed to be here tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight tonight.
We can't be held hostage by this country forever.
When will it end?
When will any leader put their foot down and re-sort American sovereignty?
Do we run the world or does Israel?
Do we even run our own punch?
Do we control our own military?
Do we control our own government or does Israel?
When I get home, I want you.
I'm not supposed to be here tonight.
I'm supposed to be here.
I'm doing drugs with a low health.
My fight says nothing but a screw in a photo.
I stretch my head but my throat just goes up.
When I get home, I want you.
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello, I got places to be here.
Good evening, everybody.
You're watching America First.
My name is Nicholas Jake Fuentes.
We have a great show for you tonight.
They believed a lion could be brought to heel.
They have total control.
But a lion could from his courage be pride.
Over every single thing.
But the lion himself would learn to kneel.
They pulled the string.
The lion would not care even if his lion died.
Things have to change.
That the lion himself would accept such a deal.
And they have to change right now.
In the end, it was only to themselves they had lied.
I am your voice.
I'm your name.
.
more and more. We demand love. What he's looking for is from desire. My nonsense is purified.
It's from desire. My nonsense is purified. It's from desire. My nonsense is purified.
It's from desire. There is something involved where we have to forgive them. We do have to
forgive them for their ignorance. We do have to forgive them for their misunderstanding and we
have to embrace them and say, better late than never. Welcome to the right side of history.
Welcome to our our massive vision, our massive and ambitious vision for how we want the world to
be.
Hello hello hello hello hello hello hello that place is to be
Good evening everybody you're watching a miracle first my name is Nicholas Jake lunches we have a great show for you tonight
When can we expect real victory, and who's going to deliver it?
J.E. Vance, if they reveal birthright citizenship, his wife wouldn't be a citizen anymore.
I know, no other country, this is my home.
Thank you, guys.
Jesus is the way and the life and the King of Israel.
We just leave with love.
We're really at a crossroads here.
Look around you.
It's drag queens in schools.
It's 18-year-olds joining Holy Phant.
It's the Philphantic talk.
It's this country not having a border.
It's the idea that our kids and we, this generation, are never going to own us.
Think about it.
Never making an income to support a family.
Never being able to have a family.
People being corrupted before.
You're even a teenager by things on their phone.
Sick addiction, the technology.
The future is so bleak.
But that has changed the calculation.
God is using me.
He's breaking me down.
He's removing all of the, you know, riches person, all of this.
So I can serve him.
I think they've been extremely unfair to you.
Who is they, though?
We can't tell you they is, can't we?
There is no future if we do nothing now.
There is nothing to use.
People that are scrambling trying to protect their ever shrinking share of what they have
are foolish.
It's all going.
It's all going away.
This country is being ripped apart and raped and looted.
We're being slowly poisoned and in some cases quickly murdered and assassinated.
And we're killing ourselves every day.
inadvertently.
With the kinds of things that we eat and breathe and drink and see.
People have got to start to radically begin to obey their conscience.
And tell the truth and do the right thing.
People have got to start to get courageous.
And this is the time for everybody to turn and look to God.
And to pray and to ask for strength and to ask for wisdom to get through this time.
And to transform and sanctify this country.
And the alternative is that there will be no country.
Is it really only as big as low gas prices?
Is it really only so big as bringing inflation and gas prices in the corporate tax rate back down?
Is that about waiting for someone to come in and change the policy and make it better?
It's a personal decision that we all have to make.
To become soldiers of Christ.
So many does not murder Charlie Kirk because they voted for Kamala Harris.
People do not stab young girls on trains because they're born black.
People do not shoot Palestinians in the back of the head or cheer it on just because they're Jewish.
The people that do this are lost.
They have to be isolated and segregated out.
A new consensus must emerge.
Are you in favor of a society with meaning?
A society where life is sacred?
Where life has sanctity?
Where people's lives and their dignity and their integrity is respected?
Or are we going to live in a society that is a never-ending war between nihilistic tribes, warlords, savages, pagans?
I see an emerging consensus and I think that the mature people that actually love America, actually love our children.
The people that recognize the division, the peril that we're in.
We need to fortify a new consensus and rally the people of conscience.
The people of decency, the people of humanity, the people of charity towards their fellow man.
Against those that want to kill us.
Against those that laugh and celebrate when innocent people are harmed.
For any reason, for any ideological reason.
Against the people that are cruel.
The people that are hateful.
And by that I mean the people that are really cruel.
Not the people that say things you disagree with.
Not the people that are provocative.
Not the people that are sometimes angry.
But the people that are really cruel and really evil.
No, no, no, no.
What makes Christianity and Christ so different from the other religions.
Is that our religion is based on the bearing of suffering for the sake of even those that persecute us.
An overflowing of love.
An overflowing of self giving love.
So much if it cannot be contained.
An unconditional, absolute standard of love for all of God's children.
Even those that are misguided.
Even those that persecute us.
Even the most heinous among us.
That is what makes us difference.
That is what makes us good.
The Canary Mission is an Israeli-funded blacklist, which since July 2025 has been confirmed
to be used by the Trump administration to target students, professors and professionals
who oppose Israel and reside in the United States. This idea is part of an initiative created
by the Heritage Foundation. The same group responsible for the infamous project 2025.
In their initiative, titled Project Dester, they state that students participating in
pro-Palestinian protests and activism are supporting Hamas, a group that the United States
designates as a foreign terrorist organization. Therefore, pro-Palestinian students are considered
to be supporting terrorism and are subject to the revocation of visas, frozen bank accounts,
asset seizures, and the denial of basic constitutional rights. In effect, the Canary Mission serves
as a means to circumvent constitutional protections, allowing the federal government to engage
in intelligence gathering activities that would otherwise be considered unlawful. But
the Canary Mission is not alone. Palantir, another company closely aligned with the state
of Israel, uses AI-driven analytics to maintain private databases on U.S. citizens and currently
works with four federal agencies. While government contracting with the private sector is longstanding,
the prominent influence of Jewish groups within these increasingly powerful organizations warrants
careful examination.
I renew the call for all able-bodied young American men, all of our elite human capital,
all of our geniuses, warriors, intelligent people to dedicate themselves to American sovereignty
and independence, as Christians, as Americans, as white people, as citizens of the United States.
And anybody that settles for anything less is just as much of an enemy I would actually
consider them worse than our oppressors.
So on Independence Day, it's important to reflect on the fact that we are an occupied nation.
Now, just like then, we're being ruled by a small country across an ocean, serving itself
at our expense, and as long as that is the case, I will always be obsessed with that.
As long as that is the case, I will always be speaking out against that and fighting against
that, and I will always be anchored, understanding that that is the fundamental struggle.
As long as our presidents have to kiss the wall in Israel and wear a small hat, as long
as they have to say that we want to make Israel great again and they're the greatest country
ever, and I will never be okay with that.
Ever.
And it doesn't matter what they offer me or us, it doesn't matter how they might try
to placate us, or appease our interests, the concessions they'll make, as long as that
is the case, it is unacceptable.
And that's what it means to be an American.
How did we get here?
This is not a timeline going back to 1948.
What had just happened before the 2016 election, Barack Obama created the Joint Comprehensive
Plan of Action, the JCPOA, or the Iranian Nuclear Deal, and Barack Obama brought together
China, Russia, Germany, France, the United Kingdom, and the United States and the European
Union to enforce a nuclear deal that restricts Iran's enrichment of uranium.
The early talks were conducted in secret, and the Israelis were furious, furious about
this.
The United Obama, Netanyahu, went to a joint session of Congress and gave a speech in
defiance of the American President, and its nuclear deal, and Congress gave 37 standing
ovation.
This is the background of Trump's first election.
2016 election happens.
Trump gets elected with the help of the Israelis.
You don't believe me?
There's a whole article about it.
It's an excerpt from James Bamford's book Spy Fail.
It goes in a great detail about the hidden collusion in the 2016 election.
It wasn't Trump and Russia.
It was Trump and Israel.
And why was Israel so hell-bent on getting a Republican elected in 2016 to scut all the
Iranian nuclear deal?
And that's exactly what happened.
That was the ask.
The United States will withdraw from the Iran nuclear deal.
In 2018, Donald Trump declares the IRGC, the Revolutionary Guard, which is the military
of the regime, a terrorist group, green lights, that group for sanctions, for attacks.
Now the United States is in a shadow war with Iran.
It culminates by January 2020 in the assassination of Qasim Soleimani.
Soleimani was the architect of the Axis of Resistance, Hamas, Hezbollah, the Houthis,
Soleimani built all of it.
Are you starting to see Obama had this solved?
He made the deal.
The Israelis hated him for it.
They colluded with Trump to get him elected so that Trump would do maximum pressure and
create a ladder of escalation, pulling us out of the deal, declaring the IRGC terrorists,
then killing its leader, putting sanctions on the regime.
This is a war that started a long time ago that Trump made hot in 2018 and has been going
on for seven years.
That's the nature of forever wars.
Just like in Iraq, which went from 1990 until today, just like Libya, which went from
2011 to today, Syria, which went from 2011 to today, and Iran, which went from 2018 until
today.
That's the nature of forever wars.
And if you're not paying attention to those underlying forces, you're going to fall for
it again and again.
You're going to be surprised and confused and coping over and over.
And people are just tripping over themselves to do it again.
And people are just tripping over themselves to do it again and again and again.
It's like I started out like the Jews are oppressing us then it's like no no the Jews are oppressing all of you
Maybe I need to help
You asked me why I'm doing all this
But even if I told you why I doubt very strongly that the knowledge would change anything
But let's say that I take the time to explain it to you. What do you think would have been there?
You
It's America first but like actually it's kind of Israel first. The Jews in Israel has so much control over our government right now
We paved the way with our corpses, brothers and all the alt-writers that got banned all the alt-writers that got slandered even people that killed themselves
Our corpses paved the way for you now to walk over
And you can't give us
The knowledge men now you want to slam the door on us. It's not right. It's not right
Oh
Okay
Good evening everybody you're watching America first. My name is Nicholas J. Fuentes
We have a great show free tonight very excited to be back here with you tonight on Wednesday
We have a lot to talk about tonight lots to get into big show
The Jews
But they know the next generation is with us and they're writing about it in the New York Times
They said anywhere between 30 and 40% of the White House staffers and congressional staffers are groipers
That's an underestimate
That's an undercount
It all means nothing if we don't get our people in office if we don't get our people in government
And that's why I tell groipers don't let them put your name on a list
Hi, conceal your views like they did
Like they did
Don't let live in put you on a list
Your job is to get into the Ivy League your job is to get into these offices do what you need to do
Say what you need to say hold it close to the chest
But we bleed for America
That's why I like to raise the right hand
You don't have to broadcast it to everybody and you can say what you need to say
When we're in private
It's America first it's Christus King
And you're not going to know how many of us there are and you're not going to know which one of us we are
And you're not going to get a good count and you're not going to know all our names
And slowly but surely you will be encircled and you will be surrounded and one day you're going to wake up in the groiper party
You
But as soon as you start playing
I
Is
I'm gonna end up taking boys and gonna do an accent trick
But girls that don't want to put them on the set
Just know how to use a couple, not a bad tip
But just stop the track and then reverse the tension
See what they said, put them on the board
And then on the board, do an o-round
Okay, one more move
It's not even a cold a second
But don't have me back with the posis
It's too much that they want to always do a reset
It's too much that they want to end up on your head
Pray before you go to bed
Every day my mind will see
Now my words, now my rules, I've been forced to write
Every morning, I have everybody here in the world
Americanism, not globalism
Will be our credo
It's going to be only America first, America first.
The American people will come first once again.
With respect, the respect that we deserve.
From this day, it's going to be only America first, America first.
Good evening, everybody.
You're watching America first.
My name is Nicholas J. Fuentes.
We have a great show for you tonight.
Very excited to be back here with you tonight on Thursday.
It is Thursday, right?
We got a lot to talk about tonight.
Lots to get into big show.
It's actually a huge show.
A featured story tonight.
We are once again getting into the negotiations between the United States and Iran on Iran's
nuclear program.
And we finally have what looks like a definitive update.
I know maybe this topic feels stale.
It's kind of getting a little bit old for me.
I like it, but there's not a lot of movement on it.
It's been probably about a month since the protests in January.
And it seems like we just have this uncertainty.
We have no idea if the US will act what it's going to be to what end.
But today, it seems like all of that has finally changed.
And as you know, this morning was the long anticipated third round of discussions between the US
and Iran.
Once again, they were held in Geneva, Switzerland.
And it seems like if there was ever a definitive decisive moment, it was this morning, this morning
our time.
And the big development is that the talks seem to have utterly collapsed.
Now, they say that there's going to be another round of discussions next week.
That's what everybody says.
I would remind you, however, that just before Israel bombed Iran last year in June,
they had scheduled another round of talks.
So to me, that does not necessarily preclude the possibility of a military confrontation
this weekend or next week, even though they say the talks are ongoing.
Now, the reason that I'm a little bit more confident today that we have some clue
as to where all of this is headed is because despite what we talked about last night,
we went to a little bit of what was said during the state of the union.
And there were some new statements from Rubio and Vance.
And we played devil's advocate.
We talked a little bit about a possibility for Trump to pursue an off ramp.
He seems to be looking for one at least.
But today, all of that was effectively debunked to the extent that there was any hope
that there is an off ramp that is viable or that Trump is looking for one.
We now know that is not the case.
And we know that because the US entered the talks today with a list of demands
and they are exactly the same.
It's the same list of demands that we've been dealing with for the past year.
And they are that Iran has to destroy its nuclear facilities.
So they actually have to go in and blow up all the infrastructure, which they've invested in.
They have to agree to never enrich uranium again.
And that's permanent. There's no sunset clause, nothing like that.
And not only did they have to forfeit their highly enriched uranium,
but they have to give it to the United States.
So there was talk earlier in the talks and the discussions that maybe Iran would give
some of the stockpile to a third country.
So they might give half of it to Russia, let's say.
Well, the United States today is demanding that they give all of it to the United States.
And so these are the same demands.
Again, this is really nothing new.
This is what they've been saying for the past couple of months.
This is what they said last year.
These have been the demands really since 2018.
Destroy the nuclear program, no enrichment, no sunset clause.
And you got to give up what you've already enriched.
And that's the deal.
Now, not only are these a list of demands that Iran is never going to accept,
but the United States isn't even offering anything in return.
Iran, if they even are going to make any kind of a deal,
and they have made some concessions, they said they might dilute their stockpile.
They might give some of the stockpile again to a third country.
They would agree to slow or restrict enrichment for a period of time.
Even if they made an agreement like that,
what Iran is asking for in return is massive and immediate sanctions relief.
Because if they don't have it, then their country is going to collapse.
They need to fix the infrastructure.
They need electricity.
They need water.
They need food.
They need things to start coming back into the country.
So it doesn't even make sense for Iran to make a deal.
And they're not going to unless they get the floodgates for investment and commerce to open up.
And the US isn't even offering that.
They're giving basically no sanctions relief.
And the sanctions relief that they're giving is contingent upon Iran's compliance with the other demands.
So it's as I said last week, the week before, this is an ultimatum.
This has not changed.
Trump gave Iran an ultimatum.
And the ultimatum is you're going to agree to all of our demands.
You give up entirely or we're going to war.
There's going to be no deal.
There's going to be no concessions.
There is not a compromise.
It's not even really a negotiation.
Trump is saying it's a take it or leave a deal.
You're either going to agree to all this or we're going to war and that's it.
And Trump has not budged.
And that was clear today.
Now the timeline is about to expire.
It was last Tuesday, not this previous Tuesday, three days ago.
It was the previous Tuesday.
So 10 days ago, I guess nine days ago, it was nine days ago that Trump gave Iran a 10 day to 14 day deadline.
So the 10 day, which is obviously sooner.
That's tomorrow.
14 days is Tuesday.
So the deadline that Trump imposed on himself and on Iran to make a deal.
It either expires tomorrow or it expires on Tuesday.
That would point toward
imminent strikes, either this weekend or next weekend. And so I think that is how all
of this is shaping up. Again, there are some headlines about maybe another last ditch
effort. They say that the Omani minister is coming tomorrow or tonight and he's going
to try to make a last ditch agreement and they say that they're scheduling another round
of talks and the Iranians say that it's going well. But how could it be going well? It's
the same program. It's been the same program since a year ago. So we are headed towards, excuse
me, we're headed towards a war. That's where all the arrows are pointing right now. So we're
going to get into that. We're also going to talk tonight about this major, major move
in the media industry. And we've had a rye on this one for a little bit and, you know,
it's being called an upset. But I guess that's only if you're not a conspiracy theorist.
So as you know, Larry Ellison, the Jewish billionaire CEO and chairman of Oracle, the software
giant has been trying to build a media empire. He has ambitions to build what will probably
become uncontested undoubtedly the number one media conglomerate in the world going
from no media holdings, basically no media portfolio at all to in the span of one year,
Larry Ellison now owns the media. And we've talked about this last year, his son David Ellison
acquired Paramount pictures for his media company, which is called Skydance. And it became
Skydance Paramount. And with Paramount, they acquired CBS, CBS news, number of television stations,
paramount pictures, paramount plus the streaming service. This is already a pretty substantial
media holding just as quickly as David Ellison acquired Paramount, they wanted to go after Warner
Brothers. And they set their sites on Warner Brothers, which is another massive media company,
and they made a bid for it. When they made the bid for Warner Brothers, it triggered an open
bid. And Warner Brothers went out and they solicited other offers. Netflix came in with a massive
substantial offer and Warner Brothers board approved that offer. And so literally up until yesterday
from December until yesterday, Netflix had a deal approved by the board. That was the program.
They were going to acquire Warner Brothers and that was it. It was looking like it was a done deal.
Well, at the last minute, Paramount Skydance came back with a better offer. Netflix gave Warner
Brothers a seven day waiver to review the offer. And now this is the big announcement today,
Warner Brothers has accepted the offer. So you're now going to have Skydance Paramount and Warner
Brothers all under the Larry Ellison Empire. That is an addition to their holdings in TikTok,
which earlier this year, late last year, broke off from bite dance and formed its own independent
company. It's a US TikTok company. Larry Ellison owns a significant percentage of that owns the
algorithm and all the data. So now you've got Skydance Paramount, Warner Brothers, TikTok,
all part of the same family. So that's CBS, CBS news, CNN, Discovery Channel, Food Channel,
Nickelodeon, Paramount Pictures, Warner Brothers Studio, all of that HBO, HBO Max, Paramount Plus,
all of that plus TikTok under this one family. And as we've discussed, Larry Ellison is a close
personal friend of Benjamin Netanyahu, huge supporter of Israel. You could say this is the
biggest push in Israel's eighth front war to make the case for Zionism and for Israel's ongoing
expansionist war in the Middle East. And now it's a done deal. So we'll talk about that too.
And really the theme of the show tonight, you really have to step back and consider
who has this administration been a victory for? Who has this been a win for?
Think about what has come to pass in the second Trump administration, just these developments
today. We're going to war with Iran to pursue regime change to topple their government.
The US government forced a sale of TikTok to Larry Ellison. Arguably the Justice Department
played a role in sabotaging the Netflix Warner Brothers deal. And now this new media conglomerate
has been created under this Zionist Jewish family. We're not even getting into tonight what has
happened on the Ivy League campuses, where the Department of Education has wielded the grants
and loans for the universities to get their faculty fired, to get their policies changed.
And so really when you look at the breadth of what Trump and this administration have done,
this is the most Jewish administration in history. And I know that sounds the way that it sounds.
But it's what it is. Who is up? Who's winning here? They have recaptured the Ivy League
universities. They're overthrowing the government in Iran, which they have always wanted to do.
A Zionist Jewish family now has the largest media conglomerate in the world, or arguably
one of the largest media conglomerates in the world. You've got the State Department and DHS
actively deporting anybody that criticizes Israel on social media. Won't let people into the country
who have criticized Israel. It's endless like this. They're talking about another MoU,
another foreign aid bill for Israel. And we can't even get half a million deportations.
We can't even get a border wall. Think about this. You are being played. Who is it really for?
I I said it in 2024. It has come to pass in 25. You have to look at not simply what is not
happening, border wall deportations, tariffs, the rest, but what is happening for others?
And how are they using the institutional power? How are they using the government to achieve it?
Think about the institutional capture that has occurred. Think about this game of musical chairs.
You got Ronald Lawter, chairman of the World Jewish Congress, his son-in-law is the chair of the
Federal Reserve. Okay, so a son-in-law of this guy's running the Fed. You have Larry Fink, the Jew that
runs BlackRock running the World Economic Forum. All the Ivy Leagues had to agree to these
onerous anti-antisemitism measures to unlock their federal money. We're going to war with Iran
after we did it last year and went to war with the Houthis. And now they have rebuilt or expanded
their ownership over the media. Now you've got the Ellison's running CBS, CNN, Warner Brothers,
Paramount, HBO Max, Paramount Plus, TikTok.
And you say, wow, and people thought that the great awakening would change things.
They thought, surely the people are aware.
How could it possibly get worse?
They say, some's got to give the goiim woke up and there's nothing they could do about
it.
Well, they did something about it.
Okay.
They did something about it.
It's called they got Trump elected and you fell for it.
They tricked you.
And it's literally this simple.
You look at Trump and you say, I see what you have done for them.
Do that for us also.
Look at what he has done for them to boarding anti-Semites blowing up, Harvard and all the
other IVs going to war with Iran, making this media conglomerate happen.
How about a free speech bill for the internet?
How about a constitutional right or legislative protections for our right to speak on the
internet?
How is that even being talked about?
No.
How about a border wall?
It's been 10 years.
No.
Hasn't even started.
How about Massey?
It goes on and on, truly.
And people think the arrangement is in reverse more on that later.
So what we'll get into all that it's, it's sort of hard to witness sometimes, you know,
it's hard to watch.
But what we'll talk about all that before we get into it.
I want our mind to smash the follow button on rumble smash a like button.
Leave a comment.
Let me know what you think about the show.
Check out our merch store, Fwentist.store.
We have the hats, hoodies, sweatshirts, t-shirts, all the merch, Fwentist.store, check
it out.
We also have our America first plus subscription.
If you want to support the show, people say, how can I support the show become a plus
subscriber?
It's 15 bucks a month.
That's the base level.
And you get access to every episode of the show, every piece of content I've ever made,
every interview, debate, commentary stream.
And you know what?
The website works really well.
So people complain that the show on rumble is a little buggy or they complain about the
lobby being too long.
We have a really good video player on the website and every show is cropped.
You have an MP3 version of it.
So it's probably the best way to watch the show.
That's America first dot plus for a hundred bucks a month.
You get access to the group chat with me.
And I'm in there.
I'm dropping knowledge.
I'm hanging out with the niggas.
And like I said, the results can be mixed at times.
I was complaining a little bit about it last night.
Some of you know, look, it's a group chat.
So niggas come into the group chat and they're off the goop.
And it just is what it is.
But it's a fun time.
And I drop a lot of bonus content in there.
So if you really want the, you really want the real stuff because here's the thing.
I can't even really say so much of the good stuff on the show because everybody just
clips it and takes it out of context.
So I can't even really be myself on the show because everybody just crashes out.
I make a joke about anything in every, you literally can't make a joke about anything.
You make a joke about women.
People freak out.
You make a joke about sloths, Albanians, Muslims, people lose their minds.
Kid Rock, Oliver Anthony.
You make jokes about this stuff.
People go crazy.
So the group chat is like, it's my safe space.
I feel free to create.
So check that out.
America first dot plus, all right.
With that out of the way, we're going to dive into the show.
Before we get into the news, I do just want to say.
So has anybody been watching this, um, Candace Owens, Erica Kirk saga on YouTube?
Where, where's everybody at with that?
I'm, I'm just curious.
I just want to take a poll.
Where is everybody at with the Candace Owens, Erica Kirk thing?
I want you to press one in the chat.
If your team Candace, I want you to press two of your team, Erica, I just want to take
the temperature because I don't really know where everybody's at.
I know the one Charlie Kirk got died or got died, which Charlie Kirk got assassinated.
Everybody was a conspiracy theorist, but now I kind of want to know how people are rocking
with this press.
One, if your team Candace, two, if your team, Erica, I'm just curious.
Kind of what the consensus is live chat's kind of moving.
Oh, wow.
A lot of twos now.
A lot of twos actually.
Okay.
Some people saying three, well, that's not an option.
It's either team one or the other.
Here's the thing.
Okay.
I remember when Charlie Kirk got assassinated and everybody jumped on the conspiracy bandwagon
and they all said it's a big conspiracy.
Everybody said it's a huge conspiracy and Israel's involved and, you know, I think that was
in retrospect, the high watermark of the JQ movement and it was really all downhill
from there and maybe rightfully so.
And I remember back then, I said, I'm willing to follow the facts wherever they lead.
If there is evidence that Israel is involved, obviously, I'm very interested in that and
I'm willing to examine it.
And if it checks out, it was verified, I'll talk about it on the show and I'll be front
center.
I'll be on the front lines.
You know that I always have been for many, many years.
I've been on the front line on this issue, but at that time, I was just unconvinced.
I never saw anything resembling evidence.
I didn't see a smoking gun.
As a matter of fact, all the evidence that we have points to Tyler Robinson.
Now you can criticize the evidence.
You can scrutinize the evidence, but we have evidence.
We have discord logs.
We have the murder weapon.
We have security camera footage.
He turned himself in.
So you know, we have all this stuff and all of it points towards him.
Now you can sit there and critique that and you can say that maybe it's all fake, but
where's the evidence that something else happened?
And I'm not talking about, oh, well, this doesn't quite make sense or how could a bullet
do this?
I mean, where's the hard evidence?
Where's the positive evidence forensic evidence?
Where is it?
And I was patient and I entertained this.
Well here we are in February and it's like, there's nothing there.
Six months almost and nothing has turned up.
We don't have another murder weapon.
We don't have any witnesses.
We don't have any whistleblowers.
You got a big nothing.
And as a matter of fact, all the things that were claimed have kind of been debunked
at this point.
The Bill Akman retreat debunked with text messages and receipts.
The Netanyahu letter that was supposed to have been misrepresented what we saw.
And Charlie was glazing Israel in it.
It's exactly what Netanyahu represented.
And the Egyptian planes, the fork, Wachachuka, we got alibis from the fort and the Egyptian
planes, she got the data wrong.
So not only is there nothing, but all the leads have gone nowhere.
All the leads have either been refuted, debunked or they end in a dead end.
Now we're on error.
Kirk. And I'll admit, I tuned into the first episode and I watched some of it. I saw some
of the clips and I saw some of the clips from today. And now the big idea, she's into the big idea
that Erica Kirk is some kind of handler. I don't even really know what the idea is actually,
because it's never been made clear. We don't, at this point, we still don't even know what the
theory is who killed Charlie Kirk or why. There's all these little things like psychics and time
travel and the French and the Israelis and Freud somehow and like, I don't even really know
what the big idea is is that she's like some kind of military spook. I don't even really know what
the big idea is. But okay, let's entertain the idea that maybe she's involved in this. What's the
evidence? And I'm watching the show and the evidence amounts to these like clerical errors.
So we looked into these divorce records and it, they had the wrong year for her marriage and
divorce in one of the filings. And he go, okay, so what? The parents got divorced and in the
filing that year is wrong? Okay, so what? If your claim is that she's some kind of military plant
and Charlie's a psychic and he can astral project and the military shut it down because they're
into magic and the fusion of science and spirituality. How does that prove any of that? How does a
how does a miss or I don't know what you would call that? I mean a false entry, a mistake. How does
a mistake on a public court filing prove that Charlie Kirk was a psychic and had ESP
and was killed by them? I'm just not seeing it. So I saw that today and I was very disappointed
because there was so much hype. It's like, okay, we're going to blow the lid French kill squads
and time travelers and astral projection and psychics and aliens and this is a conspiracy that
goes back 300 years and you go, okay, let's see. So let's get into it. Let's get down to business.
What's the proof? So we went into her to parents divorce filings from 30 years ago and they got
the year wrong and they hastily edited it with pen. You go, okay, so so I saw that and I got to
be honest. This is what I will say. And it was a little bit surprising. Matt Walsh, who is
canisowans former colleague and friend at daily wire. He came out today with the video very strongly,
very directly going after canisowans for attacking Eric Kirk. And I watched the whole video and
credit words do. You know me, I'm very critical of Matt Walsh. I believe he should leave daily
wire. I think as long as he is at daily wire, he is giving them credibility. I think daily wire
is a Zionist Jewish operation. I think it effectively exists to support the pro-Israel agenda.
And I think that the longer that Matt Walsh and Michael Noel stay there, they are delaying
its inevitable collapse and they're actually buttressing its credibility. So I have my critiques
of Matt Walsh. But I have to say I really admired his statement today. And it's not just because
I have a little bit of a beef with canisowans. It's because I think that took a lot of balls and I
think it took a lot of integrity because I know that's his friend and I know that they've worked
together and I know that he probably has to expect that he'll get some backlash for this
that maybe his audience won't be receptive to it. But it was a very powerful episode because he
said, you know what? At the end of the day, this isn't a game. He said, Charlie Kirk actually did
die. And Erica actually is now a widow. And you can take away everything else. And you know,
you can talk about the evidence and the killing and all this. He goes, but that's her life.
And she's devastated. She's a wreck. This is a horrible situation. How is somebody supposed to
react to a situation like that? Your husband gets publicly executed by some maniac.
He goes and he says he's talked to her and he's he's leveled with her and related with her.
He said, and fundamentally, it is just wrong to attack and accuse somebody with no evidence.
If you're going after somebody and he made actually a really good point, he said it better than
I did. He said, nobody is saying that Erica probably killed Charlie, but we should let it go
because he's a, she's a grieving widow. He goes, there's no evidence that she did this.
And she is a grieving widow. And you're making all these unfounded charges and unfounded
allegations, which what they really amount to is sort of circumstantial stuff. It's a lot of
judgemental type stuff. Well, we don't like the way she looks and we don't like the way she's acting
questioning some of the decisions she's made. He goes and it's just wrong to level these
unfounded charges with no evidence against a person, especially when they're going through a
very difficult time and that's their life. And I thought that was a really powerful statement.
And you know, I've said some things about Erica Kirk too. And I think it's true. I mean,
she does look a little bit phony at times and I question whether it's a good idea for it to
take over turning point. And you know, I think those are fair criticisms, but to say she's part
of the military conspiracy to killer husband, where's the evidence? That requires extraordinary
evidence. And if you make that claim, the burden of proof is on you. We're innocent until proven
guilty. If you're making the claim, we're not saying that turning point is 100%. You know, me,
I've had my problems with turning point. And we're not saying that we totally approve of that
decision for her to step up or whatever. But you're making the claim that she killed her husband
that she saw military spook. That's an extraordinary allegation. It does require evidence.
The burden of proof is on you. And so far, there's none of that. And what we get instead is a sort of
smarmy cocky attitude and also always talking about the numbers. It's always like, well, you're just
mad because my show's number one. You're just mad because our show's doing so great. You're just
mad because we're making so much money. And he goes, where's the evidence? If you care about the
truth, you're a truth teller, why you run into this person through the ringer without any actual
credible evidence? When I talk about a person, for example, like JD Vance, I bring the receipts.
He held the fundraiser at Les Wexner's house in Ohio, according to several sources. Les Wexner's
in the Epstein files. That's evidence. We talk about Tucker Carlson. You bring the receipts.
His dad ran voice of America for the CIA. Then was at the foundation for defensive democracies,
which is the most pro-Israel think tank in DC. That's evidence. That's a receipt. That's proof.
It's there. It's public record. It's, it's there. These associations,
these events, these are things that are documented. That's proof. But to say, we found a
clerical error in this public filing from 40 years ago and such and such a thing, Sigmund Freud,
and this dad and the other project looking glass. That's not evidence. And this is what I was
getting after out the year. It's just irresponsible and it's also unethical
to run a show like it's a soap opera. And this is my problem with the
conspiracy genre. It's being, it's being generated. As though it's a serialized true crime soap opera.
When in reality, well, what it should be is it should deal in reality. It should deal with facts.
It should deal with evidence. It should deal with the truth. We are in the business of seeking
the truth in politics, in religion. And if there's a conspiracy, then in a conspiracy theory as well.
But the purpose of the show is not to create this endless glut of sensationalist tabloid gossip
for women. Like it's a big game. It's not a game, but we are trying to achieve political change.
And we're in this pursuit of truth. So to do all of this, it's gone on long enough.
It has reached this point of, I think, just total exuberance.
And I actually commend Matt Walsh. I thought that was very admirable. And I think it speaks very
highly of his character. And it's a shame, you know, because I really, like I said, I've got a
lot of critiques of Matt Walsh. But time and again, I think he does demonstrate that he has character.
Even though I disagree with him, even though I really have intense
criticisms and disagreements with him and his decisions, I think he's, he's a guy with a lot of
integrity and a lot of character. And I think that he proves that time and again, you got to give
credit where it's due. You got to be, if someone's doing something wrong, you got to be critical.
If someone does the right thing, you have to be effusive in your praise also. So good on him.
But I just wanted to throw that out there. I'm witnessing this. And I'm like, you know, this
is wrong. This is just fucked up at this point. And I'm not trying to white night for turning point
at all. I know I just took a poll and said, are you on team Candace or team Erica? It's really not
about taking sides. I have my problems with turning point. I have my personal beef with Candace.
But this is wrong. You want to go after turning point, go after them for the right reasons.
You know, my critique against turning point was that they were too pro-Israel, too pro legal
immigration, too socially liberal based on things they had said. I wasn't saying, oh,
they're killing their founder. They, they conspired to murder their boss and husband.
And we brought evidence, you know, so it's a shame. It's really, I feel like 2026 is a difficult
year. I've said it. 2025 was in many ways the high watermark. I think that everybody woke up and
this became a big fat and this became a big social media trend. And now we're sort of witnessing
the fragmentation. And I think it was because maybe this stuff became so popular that it attracted
the wrong kinds of people. And by that, I mean the Jewish conspiracy stuff, the general conspiracy
stuff, it became so sensational and so popular. It truly became a phenomenon that it attracted a lot
of people who were in it because it was an endless wellspring of engagement for engagement farming.
And then therefore translating that into money, advertising dollars, a media career, that was,
that was like the next, that was the second act for a lot of different kinds of media personalities.
And even with the audience, I think the audience was attracted to it because for whatever reason,
this was being pumped onto everybody's timeline, onto everybody's for you page by the algorithm.
And so as a consequence, maybe there was this bubble effect. There was too much of it,
too much of it. And maybe the wrong kinds of people creating and consuming it. And now I think we're
in a, you could say a JQ recession. We are certainly in what I would call a JQ correction. And there
are some elements of that. It's in our conflict with the left that is Israel critical. It's in our
conflict with the Muslims that are preoccupied with the provincial concerns of their own people,
like Palestinian statehood. And it's in the skit so QAnon conspiracy stuff. I also don't doubt
that there is some element of foreign influence there. And obviously those charges are amplified
to suit the needs of the Israelis. They like to say, oh, well, every Israel critical thing is
result of foreign influence. I think we're just not being honest if we say that there wasn't any
element of that at all in the past year. And I think almost certainly you could say there was.
Now that is independent of the truth. The truth is the truth. But whether certain narratives
were artificially amplified, that is also a separate question. And it's testable. So
we have to move very thoughtfully. Everything cannot be a purity spiral. Everything cannot be
heuristic thinking. And by that, I mean, we cannot fall back and be intellectually lazy on certain
heuristics where we just blame the Jews for everything. Oh, Charlie Kirk got killed. It's Israel.
Really? Why? Where's the evidence? Will they kill everyone else? Okay, that's a heuristic.
That's a rule that has been established. That's intellectually lazy. And and then the
ceaseless idea, everything is a conspiracy. And if you don't believe in every conspiracy,
well, you're not our guy. You're a fad. You're an operative. You're a part of the psychic
CIA illuminati thing. You're a frankest.
What we are in the business of, I'll remind you, is achieving political change. And this
requires us to be extremely thoughtful and sharp and clever and prudent. And so it can't
always just be like I said, the lowest IQ loudest people in the room, the most unseasoned
people that got redpilled yesterday, the lunatics running the asylum. We have to be very careful
moving forward because this last thing I'll say, as we get into the show tonight, you will see
the Jews have mounted a counter offensive. Okay, they saw what happened last year.
And they went back to the workshop and they figured out their new response. And now I think
the momentum is with them more than it is with us. And so that requires us to be good game players.
That requires us to be good tacticians and strategists. We have actually an abundance of people
that are cheerleaders and yelling in a megaphone, chanting, chanting, the talking points. We actually
have enough of that. What we need are tacticians, strategists, people that can think strategically,
people that can think critically. What we need are genuine researchers, people that are willing
to do the boring work of doing the real research and actually scrutinizing evidence,
not going through the Epstein files and doing command find. And saying, where do they mention the
satanic pedophile stuff? And then just literally throwing out everything that we find,
even if it's fake, even if it's debunked or AI generated, we have to do the difficult work.
We are in a war. War is difficult. Games are difficult because on the other side of the table
is another rational actor on the other side of the table from us on the chess board is a very
sophisticated adversary, okay? On the other side of the chess board is a very sophisticated,
rational actor, a very complex thinker. I'm talking about world jewelry. And so if you think we're
just going to scream in their faces with the pitchforks and torches until we magically somehow win,
we
just need more anger. Just say it louder. Just say it again. Just say the same thing every
day. Jews did it. Jews did it every day. And if we just say it loud enough, and if we
just say it obnoxiously enough, somehow that will magically give us institutional power.
No. The only success belongs to people that can engage in long term planning sustained
efforts, strategic and tactical thinking, people that are sophisticated, people that are
so reminded, looking at the truth, that is what delivers victory. And that's what I'm
interested in. I'm interested in freeing our people. I'm interested in American sovereignty.
And that comes from gaining institutional power. And that's not going to be achieved
by chest beating. But people genuinely seem to think that they think that if the goi
and wake up, if the goi and wake up, and if we just do, we're going to do another rant,
we're going to do another rant on Twitter. We're just going to charge up our emotions,
more rage porn, more yelling. One day we'll wake up in the country that we want. No,
you have to build the country that you want brick by brick every day with painful sacrifices.
Don't you understand that? Painful sacrifices. And sometimes that's the pain of giving
your life to this cause. Not looking for some orgyastic moment where we go out on the battlefield
and murder ourselves and get canceled because we say the most offensive thing. I mean, that
actually feels good to do that, to do something emotive. You know, it doesn't feel good.
Seventy years of sustained effort day in, day out, grinding it out in the trenches, in
the battle, dirt on your face, getting shot at, not literally, maybe literally, but mostly
figuratively dealing with the heartbreak and the frustrations that this uphill battle,
it feels like a scissor fee and struggle. That, that is what is required. And so, you
know, it's a good thing that everybody woke up last year. I'm not going to say it wasn't
a good thing, but we now need to filter and refine and shape and what we need are the soldiers.
We need the people that are going to rededicate themselves to this on a daily basis because
it's the truth because it's important because it matters. It's our lives. It's our country.
So anyway, that's just a word on that whole situation. I see that and I think, look at
how it's just gone so wrong, you know, with, with that. But I do want to move on. I want
to get into our featured story tonight, more on this whole situation and predicament that
we're in. Our featured story, we're going to talk a little bit about the update in Iran.
And I'm not going to spend too much time on this because I, I assume you're bored of
hearing about it. I don't know. I feel like we've been talking about this exact situation
for like three years now because I've been predicting this since October 7th. So for
me, it's like, I've been telling you this is going to happen. I feel like chicken little.
This guy is falling, you know, since October 7, 2023, it's now February, 2026. And it's
like, you know, day 700, you know, here we are. But look, there's a big development today.
So as we've been talking about all week, this morning was the third round of negotiations
between Iran and the United States on Iran's nuclear program. And going into this round
of talks, a lot of people had no idea what to expect because there's been some bizarre
signals coming from the administration. I would say mixed signals. And this is another theme,
which has been present in this conversation for a long time, which is that the messaging is so
mixed. One day, you'll have the representatives from both sides saying the talks were great.
They were constructive. We're making headway. We're talking again next week. It's all great.
But then the days go by and you hear the rumors from inside the White House and they say,
we haven't budged an inch. Our red line is the same. We're going to war.
So there's all these mixed messages, mixed signals coming from the administration.
And so everything was riding on this meeting this morning. Like I said, this is the third round
of negotiations and setting the stage. Two weeks ago, Trump began this massive military build-up
in the Middle East. I should say he started it a month ago, but this build-up started to accumulate
about two weeks ago. And this is when Trump issued his ultimatum. Trump goes on true social and
says Iran is going to give up their nuclear program or we're going to destroy them. He said and
will give them a chance to talk, but we don't have a lot of patience. It's going to be a limited
amount of time, not 60 days, maybe a few weeks. And over the past several weeks, you've seen two
carrier strike groups deployed over a dozen warships, many squadrons of fighters, half of the
deployable US air power is in the region. US soldiers are being removed from vulnerable military
sites. Defensive systems are being deployed and moved into the region. So we have been slowly
but surely preparing for war. As these talks have been underway, we have been making the preparations,
the offensive, the defensive capabilities, getting ready, locked and loaded so that if the talks
fall through, we can pull the trigger. Now again, the talks are concerning the nuclear program.
And as I've said, you may be sick of hearing it at the center of this conflict is whether Iran can
enrich, can they enrich uranium? That's it. Because if they can enrich, they can make nuclear
fuel for a bomb. And on a long enough timeline, we have to assume they're going to do that.
So we have been insisting since 2018, when Trump ripped up the original nuclear deal,
that Iran has to dismantle all of its enrichment facilities, they have to commit to
never enrich again. And the stuff they have enriched, they have to give it up. And if they can
agree to that, then we can integrate them in normalized relations and we can have peace.
Well, Iran is never agreeing to that. So this is the impasse. Now Trump said three weeks ago,
those are the demands. We're not playing around. We don't care about your missiles. We don't
care about your proxies, but you have to give up enrichment. If you don't, there's going to be a war.
So we had the first round of negotiations. And these were held in Oman. They almost didn't
even happen. But our Middle Eastern allies, all the other ones convinced us that we should hear
Iran out. So we had our first round of negotiations in Oman a couple of weeks ago.
And all that was decided in those talks was a framework for future talks.
And the agreement was we're not going to talk about ballistic missiles or proxies
just the nuclear file. So then we come back the following week. And the United States tells
Iran, this is last Tuesday, not Tuesday a few days ago, but about nine days ago in Switzerland.
The United States tells Iran, these are our demands. No enrichment, give up your enriched
uranium, no sunset clauses, take it or leave it. And Iran said, well, maybe we'll give up some
of this stuff. Iran said, well,
well, maybe we're going to give some concessions. Iran said, maybe we'll dilute some of our enriched
uranium. We're not giving it up. Maybe we'll give up half of it. Maybe we'll dilute it to a lower
percentage enrichment. They said, and maybe we'll stop enriching at a high level for a few years.
And the United States comes back and says, yeah, that's not where we are.
The US came back on Thursday and Friday of last week and said, this isn't really a negotiation.
They said, our position is over here. You're way out over there. They said, and you got to close
that gap. You got to meet us where we are or else. This is very important to understand. The US
is not budging. They're not offering creative solutions. It's not even a direct negotiation.
We are speaking through an intermediary through an Omani media, a mediator.
So the US says do better. Iran comes there. Here's where prepared to give up. And this is what we're
not prepared to give up. And the US says, yeah, still not, still not what we want. So they said, we'll
do another round of talks. And the United States tells Iran submit your proposal on Tuesday. We'll
have our talks on Thursday. So the Omani representative delivered Iran's proposal. They sat on Thursday.
And this is the development from this morning. Jared Kushner and Steve Whitkoff went to Switzerland.
I say, oh, man, they went to Switzerland this morning. And they told Iran, once again, these are our
demands all over again. They said, we want zero enrichment. And as a matter of fact, you have to
dismantle the facilities. You have to dismantle Fordo, Natanz, and Esfahan. And this is permanent.
You can't reverse this. You can never go back on this. So no enrichment dismantled the facilities
forever. And they say that the stockpile of highly enriched uranium, you can't dilute it. You
can't give it to Russia. You have to give all of it to us. Nobody else. These are our demands.
In exchange, we're going to give you some small sanctions relief. And all of that will be
contingent on your compliance with the agreement. Iran rejected all those demands. This is a
development this morning. So we came in and we said, this is our list of demands. Take them or leave
them again. And Iran said, no, Iran literally rejected every single one. Iran said, we're going to
enrich. We're not dismantling our facilities. Obviously, there's going to be no permanence because
they aim to have continuity with the program. They said, we're not giving up our stockpile of enriched
uranium. And they said, if you want to deal, we need massive sanctions relief immediately. Not
small sanctions relief over time. The United States walked away and said, even if Iran made a deal,
maybe the Ayatollah wouldn't even approve of it. And on the flip side, even if the United
States made a deal, the US Senate might not approve of it. Any nuclear deal will have to
ultimately be approved by the Supreme Leader on Iran's side. And the Supreme Leader does not trust
the United States. If the president of Iran and the foreign minister are optimistic, the Ayatollah
who is the sovereign, who is the head of state is not. So even if we had some capitulation from Iran,
it's dubious that it would even stick. The reverse is also true. If the United States comes off
of our demands, it will have to be ratified by the Senate. Iran's entire problem with any kind of
peace talks or nuclear talks is that if the United States ripped up the first deal, because it
wasn't ratified, because the president was able to tear it up, how could they have confidence in
another deal? Well, if there's going to be another deal, Iran is going to want it to be ratified.
So that some other future president can't tear it up again. Well, who controls the Senate, the
Republicans in particular, guys like Lindsey Graham and other Neocons, guys like Federman on the
other side that are in the pocket of Israel. And you're going to need 60 votes to get
an Iran deal ratified. I don't know that you're going to be able to pull all those votes.
Israel will pull the strings. If they don't like the deal, you're not going to have it.
So here's the long story short. It's over. It's done. Okay, these negotiations are finished.
They say there's going to be more talks. More talks next week. There's going to be more talks
tonight. More talks tomorrow. Literally. They say the Omani representative is flying to DC to
make a last ditch effort. And Trump is meeting with his people at three o'clock tomorrow. And there's
going to be more talks. What is there to talk about? The US demands have not changed since the
beginning. And as of this morning, they haven't changed. And Iran has rejected them again as they
always have. So what is there to talk about? What more can be said that will bridge a divide here?
The most that Iran is offering is they'll dilute their stockpile, give up half of it.
As far as enrichment is concerned, they'll temporarily pause it, limit it.
They say that maybe they can have a consortium that will enrich uranium in Iran for the Arab
countries. The US isn't interested in any of this. And the US is not backing down.
So if there's not going to be a deal, if these positions are irreconcilable, then you can talk
as much as you want. There's going to be no agreement. And if there's going to be no agreement,
well, what's the alternative? Trump is going to turn all the ships around.
He's going to go to the two aircraft carriers and all these like Air Force wings. And he's
going to say, turn it all around. You know, we're good. We don't want to deal anyway.
It's there. It's going to be used. We're going to war. So this is a story. This is from the Wall
Street Journal. It says, quote, the latest round of talks over Iran's nuclear program wrapped up
on Thursday without a deal. And both sides are still far apart on key issues.
US on voice, Steve Whitkoff and Jared Kushner said, Iran must destroy its three main nuclear
sites, Fort O'Neill Tons and Eswan and deliver all of its remaining enriched uranium to the United
States. They also said any nuclear deal must last forever and not sunset. Iran rejected the idea
of transferring uranium stockpiles abroad. So that rules out giving it to Russia or the United
States. It also has objected to ending enrichment, dismantling its facilities and permanent restrictions
on its program. So they reject everything. Oman's foreign minister and a US official said the
two sides made progress and will meet again. The Omani said negotiations at the level of
technical experts will continue in Vienna next week. At least two dozen jet fighters crossed the
Atlantic Ocean from the United States, according to flight tracking data. They're expected to
join several squadrons already positioned at bases across the Middle East and Europe.
Iran has warned it would treat any attack, however limited as a trigger for an all-out response.
Now, look, maybe you're tired of the technical talk here. The reason I'm bringing the technical
stuff is because I want you to understand the state of the play and I want you to understand
where this is going. Okay. It's easy to talk about what this is really about, which is obvious.
But I just want you to know where we're going. Be that as it may. It should not be lost on
anybody. Exactly what is going on here. This is as clear cut and as unambiguous of an example,
as you can possibly find of a grand
Jewish conspiracy. And what I mean by this is that Iran is not our enemy. Does anybody
seriously think it is in the interest of the United States of America to pursue another
regime change war in the Middle East? How does that go for us? We just got out of Afghanistan.
We just got out of Syria. We are aiming to get out of Iraq. This has just happened in recent
years. What's the record there? Afghanistan belongs to the Taliban. Syria belongs to El Qaeda.
Iraq doesn't even want us there. It's a fragmented country completely. Libya is a failed state.
They still don't have a government. So what's the record of regime change? Failure. We're like
oh and four on regime change. And not only that, it costs a ton of money. Americans die.
And you know, this stuff is also fungible, meaning everything that we use and lose in the Middle
East. We can't use in the Indo-Pacific. We can't use in the Caribbean. So the United States does have
fights that are in our interest. And those fights will be for the first island chain. Those fights
will be for the Caribbean and Latin America. But everything that we use and then lose all the money,
all the equipment, the lives, the morale, all of that that is buried in the Middle East with
nothing to show for it. That is all opportunity cost that we're not going to be able to use in a
future conflict that might actually benefit us. So this is an extraordinary liability who possibly
would think that this is making America great again or putting America first or part of any kind
of golden age. It isn't. Well, we were promised is rebuilding America, rebuilding American infrastructure,
regime change in Washington. It doesn't matter who runs the Middle East. It doesn't matter who's
in charge of Iran. It matters who's in charge of the federal bureaucracy and the permanent state.
Isn't that the entire conceit of MAGA is to take the entrenched elites out of the powerful
positions and replace them with representatives of the people? And so who would think that in Trump's
second term, after his third run, after getting shot in the head, indicted all these things,
he's taking us to war in Iran to die, to spend money, lose equipment for the Iranians right to
freedom, for the Iranians quality of life. And we all know the answer to this question. It's not
rhetorical. Do you want to know who thinks this is a good idea? Do you want to know who this is a
golden age for? For Israel, for the Jews. That is who has pushed us into this war. As a matter of
fact, that's why we have the Trump administration. Why do you think Miriam Adelson gave Trump a
hundred million dollars in this cycle? Why do you think she gave him a hundred million dollars
in the first place in 2016? They have been paying the Republican Party this entire time
to sabotage our relations with Iran, to rip up the original nuclear deal, to kill Qasim Soleimani,
to bomb Iran's proxies, and ultimately in the long term to bring us to war, that is Iran's enemy.
And understand what is happening here. When Iran's regime is toppled, Israel becomes the
regional hegemon of the Middle East. Do you know what a valuable gift that is? Think about all
the oil, all the natural gas. Think about all the money in the Middle East, all the money from
their sale of oil. Think about all the trade routes. Think about all the sea routes going through the
Red Sea, going through the Persian Gulf. Think about all of the trade that happens in the Indian
ocean in the Eastern Mediterranean. Think about all of the rail, the highways. Think about all the
other utilities that run through the Middle East that are going to connect in the future, Asia,
Europe, and Africa. Israel is being handed that region on a silver platter. They will be
speaking softly, carrying the big stick in the Middle East, running the show over there.
So who does this benefit? Not us. That's not our golden age. That's a golden age for them.
Our equipment, our lives, our money. It's our ass for their golden age to defeat their enemies
so that they can expand their territory. They can control more seas, more oceans, more land,
more trade routes. It literally doesn't get more simple than that. This has been their mission
since October 7th and even before that. They said after October 7th, we're going to change the
status quo in the Middle East that has prevailed for the last 50 years. What did you think they were
talking about? They were talking about land for peace. They were talking about Camp David. They were
talking about the Islamic Revolution in 79. They were talking about Hezbollah in Lebanon.
That is what they were referring to specifically at all these wars that have been fought. They said
it's coming to an end. We are going to inaugurate our golden age. They said Trump is our Messiah. He's
our Cyrus the Great. Trump is our pagan, goi leader who will defeat the Persians and deliver a
Jewish golden age. That's literally who it's for and that's why Jewish billionaires paid for it.
That's why the Jewish media stood down and acquiesced to Trump's return to power.
And that is why you have the Republicans in Congress saying what they're saying. Look at Mark
Levin on Fox News. Mark Levin is on Fox News telling everybody you don't love America. If you don't
want Americans to die for Israel in the Middle East, it benefits them. And I told you this was going
to happen. I said this in 2024. I said a vote for Trump is a vote for a war with Iran and think of
how they tricked you. This is part of it. These Zionist Jews, they larp as right wing. That's what
that is. Stephen Miller is a larper. They're all larpers. Mark Levin is a larper. They draped
themselves in the American flag. They draped themselves in the Constitution. They hide behind
President Trump because they know he's popular and they do all of this so that they can wrap their
arm around your shoulder and say, Hey, we need to go to war with Iran. We are in business together.
We're going to make a deal. Trump is our president. This is what they do. They tricked you.
They told you in 24, you know, the Jews woke up after October 7th and we realized that DEI
isn't good. We realized censorship and the left are out of control. And that's why we now support
Trump. And you fell for that Bill Ackman wrote a letter to Harvard, the Jewish Zionist billionaire,
and said, I've seen the light. I've had an epiphany. The left has gone too far. He's a lifelong
liberal Democrat. He saw the light after October 7th, but people said, Oh, he's a Republican now.
No, he saw the Republican Party as a vehicle to deliver Israel's agenda.
Same thing with the frat bro uprising.
Remember when everybody was protesting Israel on the campuses?
And then this was rebranded as the frat bro uprising.
A bunch of Jewish students went out to beat the shit
out of Americans that protested Israel.
And people said those are the based frat bros rising up
for America and stuff, for bacon and for vapor wave.
For vapor wave.
It's cool frat bros doing it for the 80s and aesthetics
and whatever.
And you fell for it.
And that's what the Trump campaign was about.
Mass deportations, goal, the age, all these promises.
And what does it deliver a war for Israel in Iran right on schedule?
Year and a half ago, people said I just can't even imagine Trump
bringing us to war in Iran for regime change.
That's insane.
It's unimaginable.
And now it's inevitable.
Now it's unthinkable that we're not going to war.
And that is because of the coercive influence
of organized jewelry inside of our country, inside of our state
department, our national security council, our Pentagon,
inside of our media, inside of the GOP,
inside of our billionaire class, they are pushing us into a war.
This is the problem.
They have to lose their power.
Somebody must be elected president running against this.
In 2028, you cannot vote for JD Vance, who is JD Vance's gung ho about this.
He goes and makes a statement to the media yesterday
and says Iran can have nuclear weapons.
And we think that they're making them.
He said when he was selected to be the vice president,
he says, we got a punch Iran really hard.
He went to the Quincy Institute and said, we got to let Israel take the gloves off
and fight Iran.
You think we can vote for this guy in 28?
No, this is the problem.
You need someone to run in 28 that is explicitly committed to disempowering these people.
Someone needs to run in 28 and say, what the hell happened?
We were promised a golden age and no new wars and peace.
And somehow we got a regime change war in Iran.
I don't care how it happens.
I don't care how successful it is.
We are tired of being a puppet of a much smaller country.
We need a president who's going to root that out explicitly.
That's what Trump was supposed to be.
And he flipped.
So that's the situation with Iran.
I want to move on because it gets better.
The same day.
The same day as the situation in Iran is unfolding.
We get the news that finally in the drama over who will acquire Warner Brothers,
the major media conglomerate, we have learned that in the end,
the long shot bid placed by David Ellison's media company,
Skydance Paramount has now been accepted.
And the Larry Ellison family will now acquire,
in addition to TikTok, Skydance Paramount,
they will now also have Warner Brothers that other media conglomerate.
And they will form a super media conglomerate
under the influence of two pro-Israel Jewish Zionists.
And this is a story, this is from the Wall Street Journal.
It says, quote, Paramount Skydance emerged victorious in the bidding war for Warner Brothers.
After Netflix said it wouldn't match the David Ellison led companies latest offer
for the iconic Hollywood property.
Netflix pulled the plug on its deal soon after the Warner Board of Directors
said it determined Paramount's $31 per share offer for the entire company
was superior to Netflix's bid for Warner's movie and television studios
and HBO Max streaming service.
Depending regulatory approval, Paramount will own not only Warner Brothers and HBO,
but also popular cable networks, including CNN, TNT, TBS, and Food Network.
The development marks a stunning stunning come from behind win for Paramount.
Jews win again, a major of the Jews have won again.
Whoa, and no one could predict this.
That's why we play the game, right?
It's it.
It's a stunning.
I'm shocked.
You mean to tell me Larry Ellison got his way?
Stunned, stunned, shocked, amazing.
It's a stunning come from behind victory for Paramount and the Ellison family
whose overtures had previously been rebuffed at every turn by Warner Brothers.
After multiple unsolicited bids from Paramount last year,
Warner opened a sale process that ended with Netflix as the winning suitor.
When Ellison's Skydance media acquired control of Paramount last August,
going after Warner became his top priority.
Paramount was seen as too small to compete against Disney Netflix and Amazon.
At that time, Netflix was facing an uphill battle with the Justice Department,
which was reviewing the deal.
So for those that don't know, Larry Ellison is a Jewish billionaire.
One of the richest men in the world, I don't know where he stands currently,
but he's one of the top 10 richest men in the world.
He's got a couple hundred billion dollar net worth.
It comes from his software company, tech company Oracle,
which he owns and which he is the chairman and CEO of the company.
And he is also a close personal friend of Benjamin Netanyahu, very close friends.
So close that Netanyahu brought his family to Ellison's private island to vacation.
And Netanyahu called up Larry Ellison to get him out of a political jam in Israel.
Go figure the prime minister of Israel is under investigation by his own government.
Who does he call the bail amount?
An American Jewish billionaire Larry Ellison.
And said, Hey, Netanyahu said, I need the Jewish lawyer that Arnon Milchan is hiring.
Can you talk him out of letting that lawyer go so I can hire him?
And Larry Ellison said, say no more and made it happen.
This is the relationship.
Larry Ellison has given millions of dollars to the IDF.
He even offered Netanyahu a spot on Oracle's board.
So an American software giant that owns all your data.
Netanyahu would be on the board of that company,
at least Netanyahu turned it down.
So it was offered to him.
That's Larry Ellison.
Last year, his son, David, who has his own media company called Skydance,
they started a quest to create one of the biggest media conglomerates in the world.
So Larry's son, David, has this Skydance company.
He acquired paramount and that purchase was underwritten by his father, Larry.
So they formed this conglomerate, Skydance paramount.
And with that, they got CBS, CBS news, the paramount studio, paramount plus,
the streaming service, among other things.
So now they're cooking, now they got a little media conglomerate.
This deal was finalized in August.
You might remember when they gained control of CBS news,
they bought out Barry Weiss from the free press for $150 million.
And then they made her the editor-in-chief of CBS news,
where they started to change their coverage of the Israel-
a war and the Middle East in general. Barry Weiss also brought on a new news anchor, Tony
Dokepill, who is a pro-Israel Jew, who is involved in a controversy with Tana Hazee
Coates in 2024. That was the move that happened last year in 2025. Then they launched a bid
to acquire Warner Brothers. They wanted their media conglomerate to be even bigger. They
said, if we want to compete with Amazon Netflix, Apple, Disney, it's not enough to just have
Paramount. Paramount is peanuts. They said, we need Warner Brothers. So they submitted a huge
offer to acquire Warner Brothers studios, Discovery Channel, HBO HBO Max, CNN, TNT, TBS, all
these properties under the Warner Brothers conglomerate. Skydance Paramount made a huge offer for it.
Warner Brothers receiving the offer then opened up the bidding process and they started accepting
bids from other companies. Netflix came in with the better deal and the board of Warner Brothers
approved the deal. This happened in December. And so since December, Netflix was going forward to
acquire Warner Brothers and Skydance Paramount was out of luck. That is until the DOJ,
the Department of Justice under Pam Bondi began to scrutinize this acquisition. And they started
to say maybe Netflix is engaging in anti-competitive practices and maybe Netflix is going to be too big
if it has HBO Max and Warner Brothers. And so there was this idea that maybe the deal might not be
approved by regulators, ultimately, that are controlled by the Trump administration.
Skydance Paramount, the elephants were not to be deterred. So they came back with an offer
that Warner Brothers couldn't refuse. And last week, they offered a vastly superior offer, much more
money. And Warner Brothers is now taking the deal. They literally could not not accept the deal
because it's too much money. And so now you're going to have Warner Brothers Paramount and Skydance.
This is in addition to, and I mentioned this at the top of the show, Larry Ellison's acquisition
of TikTok. You might remember that back in 2024, the US Congress banned TikTok from the United
States unless its parent company bite dance sold the American side of the business to an American
company. And under Biden in his last year in office, no such deal was able to happen. That is
until Trump came into office and Trump brokered the sale of TikTok's US business to a newly created
US entity. He did that last year. Under the terms of that deal, Larry Ellison's company Oracle
will receive a loan TikTok's proprietary algorithm. And they will be able to modify it for US
TikTok users. What's more, Oracle already controls all of TikTok users data in America.
And Oracle will become one of the largest shareholders in the newly created US TikTok entity.
So Larry Ellison is by far and away the most important player in TikTok. He's got the algorithm.
He's got the data. He's got the ownership. He's got the equity. So you've got Skydance, Paramount
Studio, CBS, CBS News, Paramount Plus. Now you've also got Warner Brothers, Warner Brothers Studio
Discovery Network, HBO HBO Max and CNN plus TikTok. All of that under Larry Ellison, the close
personal friend of Netanyahu. It has come to pass. The Jews are once again in control of the media.
Is that a hateful trope? Is that an anti-Semitic connard? It's just true. Larry Ellison and his son
are Jewish. They are clearly partisans for Israel, friends with Israel's head of state.
And they have accumulated in the span of a year, one of the largest media conglomerates in the world.
And they've already made editorial changes to make it more pro-Israel.
Literally, what do you call that other than Jewish media? That's what it is.
And consider the following. Think about what has happened under this Trump administration.
Just take a survey. In addition to these developments, you might remember last year,
after the war broke out in Gaza, there were all these protests against Israel on the college
campuses at UCLA, at Columbia, at University of Pennsylvania. And the Jews were really unhappy
about it. And they started talking about suing these universities under the civil rights law.
And they talked about how these universities are anti-Semitic and they tried to get the faculty
fired. When Trump got elected, he used the Department of Education to withhold hundreds of millions
of dollars from all the Ivy leagues, forced them to come to the table and negotiate.
Otherwise, they would go bankrupt and forced universities like Harvard and Princeton and Yale
to accept onerous restrictions on what they can teach in their Middle East Studies Department
about Israel and which groups supporting Palestine are allowed on campus. And what kinds of things
can be said during a protest like from the river to the sea and so on.
So you think about like a sampling of things that have happened under Trump since October 7th
in 23 and Trump getting an office in 25, the Jews have recaptured the Ivy leagues
where there was an insurrection against Israel. It has been put down using the force of the
Department of Education where there was a revolt in the media, the media which is controlled by
the left and maybe arguably criticizing Israel in some ways. On TikTok, where pro-Palestine content
was more viral than pro-Israel content, now that insurrection has been put down. The algorithm
is firmly under the control of Larry Ellison. The entire content creation industry has been
vertically integrated under the control of the Ellison family. And in the Middle East, where the
actual war is going on, once again, situation is under control. Whereas Biden was depriving Israel
of 2,000 pound bombs and he tried to deter Iran rather than bomb Iran, try to make a deal.
Now the United States is about to pursue regime chains there. So think about who's up in this
administration, the Jews have recaptured the Ivy leagues, the media, TikTok and the Middle East.
And in every way, shape and form, this has been helped along by the GOP, specifically by
the Trump administration, by the executive branch. They have used the full force of the federal
government. It's education money, it's DOJ civil rights enforcement, using its military,
using its regulatory enforcement, using using all of these things to further the institutional
capture of Jewish Zionists over America. There's even other examples I mentioned earlier,
Ronald Lawter, the head of the World Jewish Congress, his son is now the nominee to chair the
federal reserve. At the World Economic Forum, Klaus Schwab has stepped down. He's been replaced by
Larry Fink, the Jewish head of BlackRock. Everywhere you look, there it is. And you think about on the
flip side, we're out here complaining about no mass deportations, no border wall, no terror,
no middle class taxa, all these kinds of things. And in the meantime, there is a golden age,
but it's happening for the Jewish nation. The Jewish nation is under. They are getting everything
they want and more. They are feeling pretty good. They have institutionally captured our elite
institutions. They've got Harvard, they've got the cathedral, they've got the brains,
they've got the military, the state department, they've got the White House, the federal reserve,
the world economic forum, ed Davos, they've got the Middle East, they are happy campers.
Everything on their wish list, they've crossed it off in a year. And the voters,
the forgotten men and women, the people of America, the white citizens of Springfield, Ohio,
of Minneapolis, Minnesota, the besieged citizens of New York City, Chicago, LA, we're out of luck.
Border wall hasn't happened, mass deportations hasn't happened, national guard deployments hasn't
happened, middle class tax cut infrastructure bill not happening. And Trump's biggest supporters
are put in the position of making excuses. Well, you got to be reasonable. You got to be reasonable.
You can't build a wall in a day. You can't deport a million people in a year. You can't
telling us, selling us, selling us to short end of the stick here that we're always pulling.
This is what I'm talking about. And at what point do you recognize that we are clearly the junior
partner in this relationship? If the GOP is comprised of its Zionist controllers and donors and
handlers and its white voters, its white conservative Christian voters, who is in the superior
position, it is clearly the Jewish handlers. They are in the driver's seat. They get everything they
want, no matter how unreasonable. They get what they want when they want it quickly. And we are left
making excuses. We are left coping and seething. Well, a million people left on their own, a million
people massively self-deported. We are left doing these things. Whereas Shapiro and Levin and
Custer and Lumer, they're happy. Whoa, regime change and Larry Ellison's media empire and
Barry Weiss at CBS and Harvard is banned anti-Semitism and lists for them. And in here's the here's
the little trick that they play. They make you think that you are giving them the power.
There's a sort of false humility where we, we stupid idiot white people say, well, I guess I
could tolerate Jews controlling our government if we get mass deportations. That's what people
are saying. Am I wrong? They're saying, well, it's worth it. If we could get mass deportations,
I'll tolerate some Jews in the administration. These are based Jews. These are Jews that
agree with us. Howard lot and Jared Kushner, Steven Miller, Steve Whitkoff. They're trying to help us.
They're conservative. They're based. They're the good ones. I don't mind teaming up with them as
long as we get mass deportations. And you think you are using them. You think that you are using
them for your ends. Oh, we'll give them the poultry concessions. If we get what we want,
we'll reluctantly make that deal. But it is the reverse. They are using you. They are using your
vote. They are getting you excited. They are getting you riled up about deportations and Somali
and fraudsters all this. They're whipping you up into a frenzy so that you will give them the
political support to do the thing they actually want to do. They don't give a shit about tariffs.
They don't care about mass deportations. You think they want America to be a white country?
They don't care. They go to a Jewish country club. They don't care. They just want to trick the
robes into thinking they're getting a nativist administration so that they can hire all of their
people in the positions that actually matter and do the favors for themselves. Give the patronage
to their own people. They can secure the ascendancy of their own tribe.
And how many times do we have to go over this? How many times do we have to learn that lesson?
People say, well, what's the alternative? The alternative is that we use our power.
The alternative is that we tell the GOP, if the GOP wants to succeed as an institution,
it has to be what it says it is. The GOP will die if it doesn't become America first.
We have to literally put a gun to the head of the GOP. I'm not fucking around.
Okay. That's how it has to be. What other option do we have? We've tried everything else.
You need to figuratively put a gun to the head of the GOP and say, give us the party or else.
This is a takeover. This is a hostile takeover. This is a hostage situation. Give us our party
or you fucking die. Metaphorically, metaphorically, politically. I'm not insinuating violence,
but that is we need a coup of the Republican party. We need a palace coup. We need to, again,
metaphorically, this is what I say every night. We need the young men that are watching this show
to join the ranks of the party, go to your college Republicans, go to your young Republicans,
be an intern, go on a campaign, volunteer in the administration, build up your resume.
This is like we are storming the palace, storming the palace, raising up the army. We are
raising up the militia figuratively and we're telling them, listen, your reign is over. You got
two options. The GOP will be destroyed or it's going to be America first. End of list.
There's no third option where we vote for the lesser of two evils. That's not happening.
There's no other option where we get reasonable and you talk us in off the ledge and we say,
oh, yeah, I guess we are a little hasty. You know what? We should just give you a vote one more time.
I think they're going to do it this time. It's happened every single time that way.
And you want to know where I'm getting this playbook from? It's coming from Trump himself.
In 2016, you know what Trump said? He said, if I don't win the GOP nomination, I'll run as an
independent. And they said, but Mr. Trump, if you run as an independent, surely Hillary Clinton will
win. And you know what? Trump said, yeah, but I got a lot of leverage. So I want to run as the
Republican. And if not, maybe I'll run as an independent. Don't tell me this is some crazy idea.
Don't tell me this has never been tried before. That was the foundation of this movement.
And let's not pretend like they gave it to Trump. Trump did what I'm talking about doing in 28
in 2016. The GOP tried everything to cheat him, deny him. They tried everything to stop him.
And in the end, many of them didn't even vote for Trump. Ben Shapiro didn't vote for Trump in 16.
Neither did JD Vance. Neither did many of them. They were perfectly willing to let a Democrat win in
2016. They were never Trumpers. Don't forget that. They were ready to roll eight years of Obama
into eight years of Hillary Clinton. And they said, well, we'll just suck it up.
And now those same people tell us you can never do that. You can never vote for a Democrat. You can never...
not vote for the Republican. You have to vote Republican. The alternative is catastrophic.
Really? Well, where was that energy in 2016? Before you knew the Trump was a shabba's
goi, you were willing to let Hillary Clinton win. How is that any different? How is it any
different that the never Trumpers were pleased? They were satisfied and smug knowing that they might
guarantee the election of Hillary Clinton and they were fine with that. But now you suggest we
sit this one out because we're getting a war with Iran and no mass deportations and people try
to tell you, you're a Democrat, you're a plant, something like that. They're gaslighting you.
They're gaslighting you because they don't want you to have what you're entitled to.
So you want to translate this mass awakening into political success. It starts with saying,
no, it starts with saying no to an administration that does nothing for you. It doesn't care about you,
it doesn't even like you. As a matter of fact, it wants you dead. You are worthless to these people.
Larry Fink, Howard Lotteneg, Jared Kushner, Stephen Miller, these white people that worship Stephen
Miller, he looks at you like a bunch of goi, because it's what you fucking are. He looks at you like
a bunch of stupid goi that are going to empower him and his friends so they can have their war for
Israel. And that is his MO. So it starts with saying no, I'm not going to vote for the Iran war
candidate. I'm not voting for the Larry Ellison candidate. I'm not voting for the Alan Garber
candidate and the Kevin Worsh candidate. I'm voting for someone who's America first. I don't care
who it is. I'm voting for the guy that's going to say America first. And I won't vote for anything
less at all. They say lesser of two evils. Who gives a ship? They wanted to let Hillary Clinton win.
We would have been fine then. We'll be fine now. So that's the message of the show. But we're
going to move on. We're going to take a look at our super chats. We'll see what you guys have to
say about all this. Let's take a look. That's my go off for the night. But seriously, like how do
you not recognize it? How do you not? Everything I just said is a fact. What is this administration done
other than secure the ascendancy of Jewish elites? Nothing. Nothing.
Here's your little, here's your little party favors going. It's ridiculous. Wake me up when
Springfield gets liberated. Are we still even, they don't even talk about it anymore because they
got your vote. They got your votes and now they're done talking about it. All right, we're going to
move on. Let's see. Let's take a look. Let's see what you guys got going on here. Let's see.
Classic Big B percent $20. Huge support from the Eastern Shore of Maryland. Thanks for your hard work.
Hey, thanks a lot, man. I appreciate it. Never been up there. I guess I've been a national harbor.
Is that the Eastern Shore? I don't know. Get them goblins and $20. Just finish reading River of
Darkness by Buddy Levy, Pizarro and Doray on a top tier wangs. I don't know that one. JJ's
accent $25. What's up? Just wanted to send a super chat. Have a good night. Peach emoji. Thank you.
Appreciate it. Based Wang sent $20. Hey, Nick, if we attack Iran, I'll unfortunately have to go.
Not to be gay or anything, but I've written you in my will for 25% of all my money. Talk about loyalty.
It's to the grave. My nigga saluting face emoji. What does that mean? You're going to be in the war?
I don't, I don't know what you mean by that. But listen, I disavow all violence. I disavow all political
violence. Okay. I don't know what you mean by that. Kind of free. That I think describes the
low and Q anti-Semites who fed issues with the numerous and very legion of dollars of half-animated
portions conceded, half-educated coxcoms who attach themselves to the idea most in fashion only to
vulgarize it and who character you're every cause they serve. However, sincerely. Yeah, that's kind of
accurate. I guess we've been dealing with that problem for a long time. I guess there's really
nothing new under the sun, huh? Attached themselves to the idea most in fashion only to vulgarize it
caricature every cost they serve. That's, yeah, that is pretty on the nose. That's looks maxing
in cell dumb. That's this. That's very.
$20. Erica is actually Charlie Kirkstead confirmed.
That's crazy. Yeah. Charlie Gerg was married to his dad just like a manual macron. I'm shocked
that it went there. See, or grow a percent. $20. I have to tell my word for it, but I'll run
Hubbard reincarnating as a semi-literate black woman is on my 2026 bingo card. All I need is
Paul Town intentionally triggers the singularity and I win a set of stick knives.
Okay, I think it's $25. Rape and pray for sniko. No, it doesn't matter as long as it gets done.
Come on now. No, we're just pray. We love sniko, but it's these Muslims, man. He called me a
larper. Me a larper. He goes, you're not a Roman. Your name is Fentus brother. My mom's line is
from Italy. Where do you think Rome is? Hello, my mom's line. My mom's a hundred percent Italian.
I'm literally Roman. You on the other hand, think you're Malcolm X.
Can we just say that? You look Asian and you think you're Malcolm X. You want to talk about
larping? I don't use that word with me. Do not use that word with me. Did you just say larper?
I know you didn't just say larper. Don't use that word with me. Bro thinks he's Malcolm X.
Dude, you're not even African American. You are Haitian. You are a toy. You are Haitian.
Do you think you're Malcolm X? You are not a African American. You're like Obama. You're like
Barack Obama. Bro, half white, half non white and not even black, black, but like, you know,
global citizen black. You're like you and black. You're like a fucking world baby. You're a
United Nations baby. Little bit of Filipino, little bit of Haitian, little bit of this,
little little bit of Hungarian Jew. I'm the larper. You think you're Malcolm X with the whole
costume and everything. That's crazy. Now I am right. And by the way, Spain, Roman. Hello,
Spain, Italy, Roman. So that's crazy. Don't don't use that. Don't use that word with me.
You take off your throw before you call me a larper. You put down the Zamzam and you take off
the throw and your Malcolm X glasses that then you can call me a larper. Don't use that word with
me. I say that affectionately. I like the man. I like the Malcolm X larp. But I saw that I was
like, are you kidding me? Okay. So we're really doing this. We have to open up a can of whoop ass
on sneaker. We're really doing this. Hold my wig. Hold my, what's his, what's his name?
Anthropomorphic. What the fuck is his name? Anthrogenic. Hold my anthropogenic wig.
Gonna have to throw the fuck down with this nigga. Now we love sneaker. We like it. It's all love.
It's all love. But larp. Don't use that word with me, pal. Those who live in glass houses.
I like, I like the lot. $0.90. I think it's char. No, no, come on. George sent $30. Iran taco.
I think we're gonna get it.
but we'll see.
Nephite won cent $20.
Syphazmox, the high post-added union yet he believes God
in his being has literal hands, feet, and a shin.
These solopheed, it's thinkmenolitary of a sky giant
counts his monotheism.
Yeah.
Well, their religion is crazy.
I mean, you know what they believe about Jesus?
They believe that Jesus, well, first of all,
why do they think that he was sentenced to death?
Muslims claim Jesus never claimed to be God.
Okay, so if he never claimed to be God,
why was he sentenced to death by the Jews?
Then they say, oh, well, you know, the gospel is revealed
and Jesus is the Messiah and a prophet and everything.
They say, but he never claimed to be God.
Okay, why do you get sent as death?
Oh, I don't know.
Okay, they say that when he was crucified,
do you know they believe that at the last minute
a body double was crucified instead?
A body double.
It's the Candacellans religion.
They believe that at the last minute,
Jesus was rescued from the cross,
ascended into heaven without dying
and a body double was killed, a body to,
so how do you do that?
How do you get a, and what's funny about this
is they've literally inverted the Jesus story,
which is that Jesus arrives to die for our sins,
to atone for us and that shows God's self giving love
and hence the Trinity, the eternal overflowing,
self giving love of the Father to the Son
and which is symbolized in the crucifixion of Christ,
giving His Son for us, they flipped it on its head.
No, no, Jesus said, see you later.
Jesus said, they expect one of us in the wreckage brother
and he literally had someone else die in his place.
So, and how does that even make any sense?
They say.
So it's like on the level of Mormonism.
It's just totally unserious and it's ridiculous.
And Sonny Faz, dude, it's gonna be glorious.
It's gonna be glorious when he is captured by ISIS.
I'm kidding.
Okay, he got really freaked out by that.
The other day I said, I hope they chop off his head.
I said, I hope they go like Jamal Kashoggi on him
and he was like, I can't believe he said that.
It's jokes, buddy.
I'm just kidding.
Okay, pal, because that's what Muslims do.
They cut people's heads off.
They destroy monuments.
Okay, ISIS is Muslim.
So that's what I mean.
She lists Joseph sent $25.
It's unfortunate that you can't proudly proclaim
where the merch is made anymore.
It was my favorite part.
Okay, thank you.
Neophyte won sent $20.
Sneko and Sonny Faz are okay with colonialism, imperialism
and slavery so long as it's Arab Sunis
and not white Christians doing it.
Literally, bro.
Literally, 100%
Orion Morales 085 on X sent $20.
Sage seems like a good match for you.
She looks Italian and almost transitioned
which means she has a man's brain.
Well, she clearly recognizes that it's better to be a man.
So as long as we can recognize that fact,
then yeah, we could probably understand each other.
She said, I hate being a woman.
I want to be a man.
It's like so true.
Like, it wouldn't.
Yeah, I don't know.
We'll see what happens.
She hasn't hit me up yet.
She hasn't hit me up because I'm a fucking unfuckable loser
in cell that she wouldn't even shake a stick at.
You know, wouldn't even give me the time of day.
Probably doesn't even know I exist.
It's all for nothing.
It's like I don't even exist.
I'm invisible.
But that's okay, but it's fine.
You know, but it's fine.
But it's fine.
I watch her from afar
at the state of the union
yearning, longing, such as the life.
Such is the life of an in-cell, of a driver.
I don't carry a gun.
I drive, okay?
Now, but we'll see who knows.
Maybe, maybe one day.
Maybe one day.
Uh, alas.
You know, I was looking, hey, speaking of which,
speaking of shortcomings and insecurities.
Speaking of that,
did you see this clavicular posted today
a before and after a picture of him?
And the before and after picture was like,
this is clavicular in 2024.
This is him in 2026.
Okay, and I'm looking at the picture.
I'm literally about to crash the fuck out.
I'm looking at the before picture.
You know what I see?
I see a basically good looking guy
that is six two and muscular.
So what, what is this looks maxing?
You're talking about you lost 15 pounds?
Looks maxing your orbital, whatever's our.
Okay, so look at the material he was working with.
You're already six two.
You're already pretty good looking.
You're already a, what was he?
He was a bouncer.
You're already a big, thick guy.
You're already a hunk pause.
You're all right, no, homo.
Not to be like, not to be like the ASU frame auger.
Did you see that?
What the fuck?
More on that in a moment.
But it's like, you're already a chat.
You're already a chat.
So, oh, I put lifts in my shoes and that took you from what?
Six, two to six, four mother fucker.
Oh, I leaned out.
I lost some of the fat in my face.
Otherwise known as going through puberty.
Otherwise known as,
this is the black pill, okay?
Aggie, if you can hear me, you were right about everything.
You were right about everything.
Insell rage.
Insell rage is back.
Okay.
Anyway.
But did you see this thing with the ASU frame auger?
What and the fuck is going on there?
I saw this video.
So he's got like a Jewish sidekick and dude,
they're in the car together.
And the ASU frame auger's like calling out
Androgenic or whatever.
Anthrogenic, I don't even know the guy's name.
But the frame auger is calling him out
and the Jewish sidekick is like playing with his hair.
Wow, I'm sorry.
What literally was like twirling his hair.
Literally had his like hand on his neck
and was like, was like doing this.
And it's like, listen, I know I'm not one to talk.
Okay, I know I've had people say I've had moments.
I don't really know what you're talking about,
but it's like, but that's crazy.
People get on my case because I'm smiling
and I look at my friend in a loving way, you know,
because I'm a loving guy.
People get on my case because I'm like, you know,
because I look at somebody smiling
and they say he's looking at him and again,
dude, twirling the brother's hair with your fingers.
I know I've never done that.
So what's going on there?
That was crazy.
That was actually crazy.
I thought, I thought I was watching call me by your name.
I thought I was in theaters, call me by your name
back in theaters, because that was next level.
That was crazy.
And he was in the middle.
It was so funny because he was in the middle
of calling him out.
He's like, he's like anthropogenic.
You don't mock shit, dude.
Can you stop playing with my hair?
We're live.
That was wild.
So anyway, yeah, I don't know what's going on.
I don't know what's going on.
with our looks, Maxgers. One of them's getting his wig snatched right off his head. The other
one's getting his hair played with and isn't even white. The guy's a, you know, fucking
towel head. So clearly, clavicular emerges as the figure of our age. Clearly, he emerges
as the dominant figure of our age in the age of Braden Peters. Truly.
Catherine Alexandria sent $20 W. Sage. Imagine escaping the Transpocalypse, being so chill and
beautiful at so to meeting the emperor of the all America's empire, then ascending
into greatness. The groypads are rooting for you sage. Let's just not, let's just not
overdo it. Okay, if we look too thirsty, we can't look too desperate. Okay, let's just
let the game come to us. The clip is out there. Catholic Taliban grover sent $40. Pray for
in rapes, Nico. No, no, just pray. American Bitcoin just $20. Humanity isn't ready for
mass racial intermingling. Colorblind unity is ideal, but impossible while war exists.
Mass Bitcoin adoption could end war by removing financial incentives. Until then, races should
largely stay separate to avoid inevitable violence. This is the truly humanitarian stance.
Selective immigration only. Mass Bitcoin adoption will end the race war. That's a new
one. I've heard a lot of Bitcoin theories in my day. Bitcoin is going to end the race war.
I don't know if Bitcoin's going to do that. It can do a lot of things. It's me Ryan Gosling
sent $20. I'm going to do that. I'm going to do that. I'm noticing the antagonism towards
the crew. You have any questions. I can send some super chat answers. Not too many. I'm
a brokeie. You are right. Don't underestimate their intelligence. Super smart crew saw
the guy rivaling you. Maybe their geo analysis basically mirrors yours. Good show TV H.
It's good when the women aren't talking. It's crystal ball is a knucklehead, but Ryan
Grimm's good. The problem with the Indian is he's seething all the time. He's like seething
calling me a racist. Here's my problem. Okay. Because I do like some of their coverage.
Like I watch their show. I like their coverage in general, but they just they're not ready
to talk about the problems with the left. You want to be liberal. That's fine. Honest
to God. You want to be liberal. Knock yourself out. But what is with this anti white stuff?
Ryan Grimm is going to support Ilhan Omar. What do you have to say about her antagonism
towards white men? That's bullshit. And you can't have that. If you want liberalism
to be attractive, it can't be anti white. And I don't even want liberalism to win. I'm
not saying it like I do, but they have this message like, well, we're normal and we're
liberal and we're tolerant. Okay, but where do the white men fit into it when you're calling
us disgusting and the enemy and dangerous and attacking our heritage? So there just seems
to be no recognition of that. And that, that is the problem.
Brandon zero six hundred twenty dollars. We understand Sneco has been real, but do you really
think he's a smart guy when he endorses Candace says America isn't inherently Christian
and sheels for Somalis. Just a third world. He's got this like chip on his shoulder.
I don't know what his problem is.
Those seven of slash sent $20. Have you seen all the John Kerriako clippers money spent
to gain youth recognition? I bet he'll announce a run for something as a live slash and
change candidate jail me slash by Obama slash did the right thing slash, etc. Yeah, it's
it's all a conspiracy, bro. He's he's a conspiracy to everything's a conspiracy. I know.
Send $20. Take the golden abundance. You know, the deal just fell through the person who
is doing the deal just like misrepresented to us basically. We thought we were getting
one thing. We got far less than they than the intermediary said we were getting. So
I said, it's not worth it anymore. So I don't even think we're going to do it. You know
what the problem is? This is what you'll find. I shouldn't have even said anything. But
what you'll find in this industry is people are just time wasteers and people just come
and say, Hey, we're going to give you all this money and then they just don't. So it
basically just never materialize.
I'm going to get blamed for it forever. Anyway, John Michael Vincent sent $20. How are
we supposed to contact you if we have services to provide for the movement? I don't expect
you to be checking Twitter. Demise, uh, well, I do. And you could shoot me an email also.
No, I sent $20. The Treaty of Tripoli was only written to protect our ship slash trade
in the minute of holy war. Secularizing the gov was done to prevent friction between
the denominations on already majority white Christian country. Everything I see from
sneakily is just third world is slop going after America or whites. Well, and that's
my thing. It's like, I have no beef with sneaco, but every so often, he just starts this
up again, where it's like we're making fun of Jesus, we're making fun of Christianity,
America, a shitting on the West. And it's like, you know, we can't take that land down.
So that's it's always the same tag.
It's a merchant sent $20. Hey, Nick, love the show. Keep up the good work. Why are communists
and capable of understanding the difference between being a colonialist and a Zionist?
Are they willfully ignorant or retarded? Anyways, I watched La La Land because of your
high praise of it and it was fucking gay as fuck. Well, you didn't get it. That's okay.
Um, it wasn't for you. It's not made for you. You should be watching the football game in
gym shorts. That's maybe more your speed. Can I get you a Miller light to go with the gym shorts
and the big game? You fucking stupid idiot. You fill a steam. It wasn't for you. Go watch fast
and furious 17 dumbass. Maybe I'll appreciate that. La La Land is who we are. It's our heritage.
That's Los Angeles. You know, and you want to know what else? You know, you want to know
what else? Let me tell you something. I'm going to tell you something about La La Land.
Do you remember when La La Land came out, it was competing with Moonlight and what was Moonlight?
It was the wokest, gayest, blackest, most niggered out movie you've ever seen in your life.
This was peak Obama wokeness. And La La Land was so refreshingly white. So refreshingly white
and beautiful. And it was an homage to America singing in the rain, Hollywood, LA,
the city of stars. That's a story of us. That's a story of America. People that moved to LA
in search of a dream, just like how the settlers moved to America in search of a dream. LA,
the frontier where dreams are made and people go there seeking glory and fame and recognition.
And it's an homage to these people in this town and our American way of life and our dominant
culture. In the same year that you had Moonlight, which was gay niggas kissing, gay niggas kissing
the movie. So that's why La La Land is important. Okay. This is the importance of La La Land.
You got gay niggas kissing the movie. Here's all the global globes. Here's all your golden
globes and the Oscar goes to La La Land is who we are. Okay. LA, Hollywood, California.
We have to have a global idea of America. Take pride in this. California is ours. It's American clay.
The mountains, the beaches, the vineyards, the hills, the industry. I mean, that's who we are. That's
America. When Europeans watch movies, they don't make movies over there. They watch American movies.
They come here and they see the yellow school buses and the red fire hydrants. And they go,
wow, it's just like the movies because that's the long arm of America. It's who we are.
And La La Land is a homage. It's a testament to the movie industry, to our glorious culture,
to our way of life. It's a city of dreamers. LA is a city of dreamers. Well, at least it used to be.
Now it's a city of, I don't even know what Mexicans dodgers fans. Now it's a city of taco trucks
and homeless people at Santa Monica Pier and well, Jews obviously. And I don't know like YouTubers.
But at one time, a 10-
years ago, 15 years ago LA is like where you went to make it big. I'm gonna be in the movies.
I'm gonna be in show business. There's something romantic about that. You would recognize
that if you ever yearned in your life, okay? Maybe you would appreciate this movie if you
ever yearned, okay? If you ever had music in your soul, okay? You douchebag, you pretentious
douchebag. So anyway, like I said, why did you go to Buffalo Wild Wings? Isn't there a game
on to catch somewhere? It's hockey season somewhere. Isn't it football season somewhere? Shouldn't
you be at a Buffalo Wild Wings or some sports bar in your basketball shorts watching something
on TV? You fucking douchebag? Asshole? La la land is for us. Anyway. So I love that movie. Great.
It's coming back. It's coming back in theaters. So I don't know. Maybe I'll drop in and watch it.
Regal cinemas bringing it back to the theater. That's how I knew about, okay? But it's coming back
to the theaters. I'm going to watch it again. Great, great music. So fun. And it's, what's not to like?
It's Emma Stone. It's Ryan Gosling. It's the music's great. It's about LA from the director of
Whiplash. What's not to like? Tell me. Anyway, I thought it was fun. One of my all-time favorites,
definitely. I'm just like a big Ryan Gosling stand as well. I just drive only God forgives,
place behind the pines, blade runner. What else is he in? I'm just a fan. So anyway. But that's a good
one. That's a good pearls before swine. Exactly. Dark Knight sent $25. New to the movement here.
On a polygenic white American. How did the Groyper movement adopt its frog mascot? What's the
lower AF? Well, many years ago, okay, before you were born, when your mom and I were young,
non-kidding. Well, back in the day, you had Pepe. You had Pepe the frog, you know, viral sensation.
And then everybody created these variations on Pepe. And so you get Marv, you get Opu, you get
Groyper. And one of the variations of Pepe was, it's actually called the, excuse me, Easter Toad.
And for whatever reason, people started calling it Groyper. Nobody knows anymore. Nobody knows.
The library's been burned to the ground and no one knows. And then I drew the first Groyper.
I drew it by hand and I christened it Groyper. I came up with it myself. Just came out of my mind.
And I, and Groyper, I created them. That's how I drew them. It's how I named them.
And that was the name given to my fans and the rest is history. And there is no other,
there's no other lore. And if you've heard of that, it's a lie. No, I'm kidding. There was a guy
called that Groyper. I don't know who he is, but he just started calling it a Groyper.
And then Groypers were just synonymous with like far-right internet,
Twitter posters. And then I just appropriated it during the Groyper War.
My fans were going to the Charlie Kirk events. And during one of the shows,
I said, imagine your Charlie Kirk and you look out at the Q&A line and it's like
three dozen Groypers ready to ask you about dancing Israelis. And at the time,
I meant as like a joke, like ridiculous Groypers that are going to ask about Jews.
I was like, that's so funny. And then it just stuck.
So that's the story. $0.20.
Trump is losing the existential war at home. Anything is fine from crushing the left as insignificant.
AI is going to usher in a totalitarian surveillance state. And if the Dems get power, it's all over.
Dude, it's already over. Okay.
Jape will $5.26. $0.20. You're my role model, Papa.
Thanks. It's already over for all of us.
$0.20. Candace doesn't believe a word she speaks. Otherwise, she wouldn't speak quickly.
I see through her. She is a survivor and will discard her husband when the coffers dry.
Props to him overmold too.
Sue her over.
So I'm overmold.
Shinsuck said $0.20.
I keep seeing the go and say that Galein Maxwell is not actually in prison.
And that the person we saw in the deposition video is a standard body double crazy work.
Yeah, that's just like next level.
So still ready to send $0.20.
If we're attacking you and I just want for us to take all their riches and oil,
then let's deport the Indians to Africa and the Africans to India.
Dude, that's delusional.
Chopin Howard pushing a woman down the stairs Groypers sent $0.20.
What is your favorite speech in the symposium?
I don't know. I couldn't tell you off the top.
PG sent $0.20.
RIP's quality potty.
Hey, I still got one.
Dollar Mike sent $0.20 really start.
Looks like our powerful allies will only be sleeping until 11 tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm going to try to get the show started earlier.
NFL and he sent $0.20.
Sneakow is pushing it.
This brown cloud is literally showing in 4K how Islam took over the Middle East.
Barely conscious in bread browns aligning with an ideological belief equally retarded as them.
Well, and it's they don't even make a defense of their religion.
It's all just cheap point scoring.
It's all just like, well, you're a hypocrite.
Well, what about this?
What about that?
It's all just like these cheap deflecting things.
Nikolai seal sent $0.50.
Sir, can we get a statement on the creator of the squatty potty being arrested for CP?
Listen, we have to separate the art from the artist.
That's always been my approach, okay?
The art from the artist.
Just because you squat to poo doesn't mean you're a pedophile, okay?
It's natural.
I mean squatting to shit.
Probably $0.20.
This blinds only real interacts with the glorious Slavic people
is when he was next to Luca at the stalls.
Caught a glimpse of his big Balkan cock and his mouth watered.
Okay, what the f?
All right.
What the f?
Sometimes I just play these without even looking at them.
Okay, thank you for that.
Big Luca sent $0.20.
Beener.
Yeah.
It's true.
Little bit of bean.
Refried bean.
They are $0.14.
Verbaly abused me if you've already spoken on this,
but if you've seen Matt Walsh's video on the achievements of white people,
dude is coming around.
I'm sure he will be next to get asked by DW.
Holy delusional.
This is like it's so sad watching the glium get tricked and tricked.
Sometimes I wonder how dumb these glium sometimes can be like holy.
Have you seen this Matt Walsh video about white people?
I think he's coming around.
You were just born to be deceived.
You were just born.
You're a shovel-faced idiot.
You were born to be tricked.
Like, what even?
What is there even to say at this point?
After all of this after $7.75, the great awakening has happened.
But as you said nearly every week, movements stay time.
Have a longer time horizon.
It starts with 2026, but this is all long-term.
Stay strong, you slow vapes.
Also, sage Blair sort of bad.
DS set $100.
Will your groipers be granted golden visas in 2036?
Okay, yeah.
Thank you for the big super chat, then, and then, and then, and then in 2036, then.
NJF is right about everything sent $20.
Sure.
Many Muslims crashing out on you just for saying this is a Christian nation law.
How is this even up for discussion?
Goes to show these clowns don't give a shit about America or our people.
Muslims have been seen online ever since Christian's apologists have mainstreamed the
Islamic dilemma proving Islam to be false.
Very true.
It's just for $20.
Big shocker.
These really are good at covering their tracks.
Watch the close-up video and read the autopsy report.
Yeah, they have alibis, but Charlie's assassination got their going puppet elected.
Where's the evidence?
What's the close-up video I did?
He got shot in the net.
Get a low par $120.
Rate that he sprinkles.
Just a girl sent $100.
Dear Nick, very nice tie.
Hey, thank you for the big super chat.
Just a girl, huh?
I don't know.
It's Thai socks.
It's Thai's quins.
No, I'm kidding.
Thank you for the big super chat.
You like this tie?
Yeah, it's all right, I guess.
It's all right as far as ties go.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Big shout out.
The Groitbats were fighting the other.
day. I'm in a group chat with all these droipats. I popped in from time to time. And there
was just this drag down. What is what is the expression drag down knuckle down? What do
they say about it? It was a fucking brawl. It was a brawl. Hair was flying everywhere.
Bitches were getting smacked and scratched. Hair was being pulled. It was something. The
droipats are vicious. I was like, damn, it was crazy. But yeah, no, I appreciate it. Thank
you very much. W. Groife at 21 dollars. You sent one for Candace and two for Erica. But
can't a nigga get a six seven? Can a nigga please get a 1488? And can we pretty please
get a hashtag rapes? Nico basal the negro slayer. That can't be the real basal. That's too
shy. Next hop guy said $20. Sneakow is a complete subversive. Pushes cause our theory.
His long takeover and multi racial working class and decennatism. Look, he's my friend.
He's my friend. I disagree with him. But he's my, we can be friends with people we disagree
with. Okay. And sneakers my bro. He's my brother. What up brother? Bang. That niggas my brother.
You know, so listen, some of these niggas. They're a little lost, but they'll find their way home.
My nigga will find his way home. We'll leave a light on Kevin Lincoln. They'll be on
$22. Hey, Nick, I'm a trad Catholic stay at home. Dad with six to seven other grown
rappers raising their homeschool children to be freedom fighters in Gavin Newsom's California.
What skills and strategy should we teach our children to fight the communists in California?
I've had my kids read the art of war, but I'm running out of ideas.
That can't. That's not real. That's not real. That is not a real super chat. That is rage bait.
You are baiting me. You are intentionally trying to make me angry. I recognize that. I
recognize that. And I'm not saying 100 dollars. Fuck both those lying ass bitches is my vote.
Both Shady and corrupt. Good to have said. So also unmute me on live chat bag. America first.
I don't run the live chat, but thank you for the big super chat. Appreciate it. Thank you.
Yes, and $20. Zerka vindicated on the square. Zerka's got it. What's the guys deal?
Skies got some big problem. Cheney 51 cent $20. I want to solve it. We got a problem.
Let's solve it. Cheney 51 cent $20. I watched Candice's show just out of curiosity and to have a laugh
at all the mispronounced words, but she is showing why women really should not be allowed to speak
about no one benefits from it. Well, you know what? In her defense, the latest clip, she said that she
didn't know that thunder is the sound of lightning. Did you see this one? In the Canis Owens trying
to read Twitter account, they found this old clip where she says she goes, I don't know if this is
a woman thing, but I didn't know that thunder is the sound of lightning. I never made that connection.
In her defense, that is 100% a woman thing because women be not knowing anything. Women don't know
shit. Every woman you will ever meet will eventually say something like that that men will not.
Women just don't have any intuition about the way anything works for some reason. There's
like this test, they give this test to college to not college aged, but to women in college.
And the test is they say, look at this bottle or glass. And they say, do you see where the water line
is? They say, now if you tilted the glass 45 degrees clockwise, they say, draw the water line.
Where would the water be? And women in college reliably get it wrong. If you're a guy, what would
you say? If you take a glass and you rotate it, where would the water line be? It would be parallel
to the ground. Obviously, parallel to the surface. Women draw it as though the water moves with the
water level doesn't change. So it's like, that's a woman thing. Women just don't understand
basic stuff like that. And you will be surprised at the things they don't know because they just don't
really think, you know. So in her defense, that's a woman moment. That's not even a dumb thing.
That's just a total woman moment. Oh, thunder is the sound of lightning. I never, you're like,
it's like you're 35 years old. You never made that connection. That's crazy.
But that's women. Cheney 51 cent $20. I just read that one.
CE cent $20. Their only strategy is to lie and cover up. The day upstein got killed. They said
security guards fell asleep in the cameras. We're out and he's decided himself in perfect time. It makes no sense.
So it's no wonder people go to crazy conspiracies because all the top voices just lie or ignore. Yeah, good point.
Cent $20 to clarify. Neserous slash jazz R was absorbed into the greater queue. And on Lord,
the things crazy shit along Candace Owens lines nowadays with reptilians in a shadow war against the
gobalan aliens and shit. Also, new merch idea gang doesn't grow or harass negative going hard as
fuck for when the non-whites are down for the cause. Big but dinky bones sent $25 couldn't keep
PhD down. So two gumball sent $20 tomorrow. Can you talk about Iran for the six million time?
It's almost like Iran matters more than the left taking over the USA. Rum fell from within. Try
focusing on America first. That's crazy. That. Oh my gosh. Okay. Well, you're just an idiot for even
thinking that out loud. Sorry. Well, let me get back to the news that really matters. Forget
about the imminent war in the Middle East with our military. Let's talk about that Super Bowl
halftime show. It should be in English now to the stuff that really matters. I'm here to
arm you at the facts that matter. The Super Bowl is in English. It's American. But why is the
halftime show in Spanish? Can anybody tell me that? You're right. These are the real stories.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Enough about that war in the Middle East or whatever. That's over there.
When I tune into the halftime show, I was surprised that the entertainment was not right wing.
All things gets to grow for $0.20. I like sneko, but the Negro has been shipping out today
about you talking about Muslims in Times Square and the Jews. As if we never talk about the Jews,
holy brown cloud moment. That's what I mean. It's always deflection. Well, what about the Jews?
We don't want either of you there. Hello. And the Jews doing the thing in Times Square is
the least of what they do. As if we don't talk enough about Jews and say, he'll send $0.20.
Can you name the four state capitals that have the same first letter as their respective states?
I don't know, dude. That's just trivia. Okay. No, Clark sent $0.25. I like sneko,
but he is intellectually dishonest about church history and American history.
Brothers for sneko that God would soften his heart to accept Jesus as Lord.
Yeah. Very true. I grew up for $0.20. Subnicker. Please stop talking about
Candice. I'm so bored of that woman. I hope she and Eric that kill each other.
Travis Kessinbaum has been daring you to a debate on X without tagging you daughter. You game.
No, he's an ankle bider. He's a Jewish ankle bider. Why do you talk to your Jewish handlers and
they could give you a media career? I'm not giving a Jew a ladder up to success.
Who are you? You aren't you are suing Harvard
in the grand scheme of things. What does that do for me? You have no cloud. You have no fucking
fans. You are nothing. You think you have a debate with me because you're a fucking Jew that's
suing Harvard for racism. Fuck you. Jews are so entitled. They think I'm going to help them.
Where were the Jews helping me? I was challenging Jews to a debate. They tried to destroy me. Yeah.
Okay. Why don't you call your uncle, see if it could get you a job, dumbass.
No, $0.95, $0.20. Violently great sneko and then pray for him as he's okay. Come on. Come on.
Come on. $0.1369. Why send $0.20? Candice strikes again. She pronounced him a degree instead of
imagery. Bitches start maxing probably a flood. I didn't see the tailor worth $0.30. I wasn't
thinking anti-revolutionary thoughts, but I'll self-flagulate just in case. Also, Oliver Anthony
made a lot of money off the song. You hate that his wife divorced him and took half his shit.
He made a song about it called Scornful Woman XD. That was awesome. That was a W. Well, it's kind of
gay, but I kind of like that he trashed his science and set $100. There is a restaurant on Harlem
and 85th and Bridgeview called Holy Pinos. How long Mexican grill? I don't remember seeing that.
It looks new. I think the name is hilarious and the concept is a-
If Sneco comes to visit, you can buy him a taco.
Just keep in mind that they are closed for lunch during Ramadan.
Hey, thank you for the big super chat.
I will not be going there.
We have plenty of good Mexican restaurants that are not.
That's just like an abomination.
That is just abominable.
You start going south on Harlem,
and you get into this weird territory where you're like,
where the fuck am I?
Like I'm in the Middle East.
So I don't even go that far south on Harlem anymore.
Or even out that far west,
you start to get over out into like,
well, like Lombard and out there.
And it's like Muslim takeover.
Tyler, you're done sent $20.
Is there a threat of Russia and Slash
are trying to come into 80 ran bricks?
Nope.
Basel sent $20.
They thought they had seen the last of me.
Birthday wishes to come through.
Happy birthday, King.
Free basil till it's backwards.
Hey, W, by the way,
you're welcome that I hooked you up.
But it's true.
Imagine shooting a man with your last bullet.
Basel stands there on phase.
The Taliban wins again.
Taliban wins again.
Hey, hook me up with little Taliban money.
Okay.
Can you hook a brother up?
You know, Saudi Arabia is not calling.
Russia is not calling.
Iran's not calling.
Can you hook a brother up?
Can I get a little Taliban money?
Or at least like an F 35?
I mean, can I get some of the stuff they left behind over there?
No, but I'm kidding.
Congrats.
I'll give you a bag, buddy.
W.
Biggie though.
Set $100.
Jews are trying to win up her number.
One anti-Somite Walt Disney now.
Nah.
Let's reach for him.
Need to get our arms around this.
Hey, thank you for the big Super Chat.
Yeah.
Very true.
Very funny.
Francesco sent $100.
Found a cute little broiker buddy outside my house last night,
like an actual frog.
Relax.
Broke him inside and he just sat in front of the screen,
staring at you for like 40 minutes of the show.
He knew he was watching the Supreme Groiker leader.
True story.
Not even a bit.
W show.
W frog.
That's cute.
We like frogs.
Thank you for the big Super Chat.
Animals love me.
I'm a lovable guy.
So that's nice.
That's a sign.
Toji Fushigura said $100.
If you had to guess, when do you think is the latest
the US strike could occur?
Mid-March?
Or could you see this stretching out till the end of the month?
Why you want to bet on polymarket?
Yeah, there's $50.
I know.
$150.
When test is our voice.
Nick Funtest slash my tongue even collab.
Hey, thank you for the huge Super Chat.
You know, I actually met him.
I met him at the NYYRC gathering.
And he's great.
Very funny.
Very precocious.
So I'm a fan.
I wasn't really sure about him, but he was cool in real life.
I don't know.
I feel like he's just going to clown me.
And I'm just not going to be able to deal with that.
Like I'm.
You know what I mean?
So I think about doing a show.
I mean, he, I don't know if he's invited me or not.
But, um.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like that.
I'm not.
Mentally durable.
That's just so insane that you would even say that those are just numbers in a press release.
$80 trillion in investment.
By the way, all those foreign investment numbers are fucking fake.
Literally Google it.
Those are all inflated when they say we're bringing in $18 trillion in investment.
They'll typically take a deal that has already been made or product that is already being
purchased.
And then maybe they'll increase it like 10%.
And then they'll take credit for the whole sum.
So that is totally inflated.
Just you don't even know what the fuck you're talking about.
That's one.
And yeah, we've had no tariffs.
We had tariffs.
Now we got to give all the revenue back, stupid.
They brought in more revenue than any, and we have to give it back with interest.
Well, the tariffs brought in all this revenue.
Yeah.
Well, that'd be a good thing if we could keep it, we have to give it back.
And then some, but you're just, you're just literally guzzling propaganda.
You are just a shameless glutton for propaganda.
You're sticking your big snout in the trough eating propaganda from the GOP.
Their press releases, their bullshit numbers.
They brought it record revenue.
Yeah.
Did you see the latest?
We have to give it all back and more 18 trillion dollars in investment, fake Google it.
So yeah, that's just crazy.
You can't just uncritically consume press releases from the White House that that's what
they do.
Okay.
Trump always talks himself up.
It's always bullshit.
It's like the wall.
There's no border wall.
Oh, we finished the wall.
No, you didn't.
And they count on suckers like you to just not do the home.
Susco, Adrienne sent $20.
Can you explain how supply of houses are going up at so early prices?
Is it the billionaires driving up interest rates?
Well, no, the federal reserve increased interest rates.
That's a huge part of it.
Okay.
Interest rates are higher than they've been in a very long time.
You had near zero interest rates for basically 20 years ever since the housing bust in 2006,
the federal reserve lowered interest rates to basically zero.
And you know, they went as low in 2020 is like 2%.
And then when all of the COVID inflation happened, federal reserve ratcheted up the rates.
And so it became more expensive to borrow.
And then the other problem is that demand is outpacing supply.
So they're building more houses, but you have all these people coming here.
And a lot of it is zoning.
A lot of it is a zoning issue in particular cities.
You know, they talk about we need to deregulate and account for these like missing middle type
projects like what do they call those like mother-in-law dwellings in the backyard and two
or three unit apartment buildings and things like that.
But yeah, interest rates are higher.
So construction costs are going up, insurance is going up, homeowner's insurance is going
up because the cost of goods went up, homeowner's insurance is supposed to replace anything
that's destroyed.
Well, if lumber is more expensive, if copper is more expensive, appliances and chips are
more expensive, then the insurance goes up.
Construction costs have gone up.
So there's a lot of reasons home prices are increasing.
The billionaires drove up the cost, that's, I don't think that really explains all of
it.
Spas are sent $20.
Sneak goes friend, the winner who he stood next to at the time square event threatened
to kill two Christian YouTubers.
God logic and Drake.
One of them in person.
The fact that he hangs out with these mouth-breathing freaks is astounding.
Yeah, they're, they're not, these people are bad news.
Christians are like loving and decent Muslims or they have hatred in their hearts, a lot
of them, not all of them, but a lot of them.
Tommy Goy sent $40.
You should do an interview with Andrew Wilson.
I would collab with him.
I don't know about an interview.
I think we both know each other.
But I would collab with him.
I like him.
I like his wife too.
They're good people.
Basement while they're sent $20.
Dems rob you and give it to their degenerate voter base.
GOP robs you and gives it to the global Jewish puppet masters.
Yep.
What's the righteous Chungus boy to do?
Sit it out.
Almost blue grow by percent $20.
The Muslims are treating what you said about sunny as a death threat.
These people are nothing but liability.
That's totally insane.
Alex Bacheco sent $22.
There's three white people that work in the kitchen at my job, including me and we were
talking about white people being a minority in America.
You got brought up and everyone was saying how much they love you.
I wasn't expecting that kind of reaction, especially from the colored people around
low.
Hey, dude, colored people love me.
Colored people and negas, they love me, Mexicans, because I'm a real, they, they know there's
no hate in my DNA, you know, but I'm, I keep it real.
So we love the negas.
Thanks.
I appreciate the law.
Just keep sent $35.
80% of the Quran is plagiarized from the Talmud, defending the line on YouTube breaks
it down.
Suhrit 2151 copied from Berrishi 3813 during Fattra, which was originally a children's
story.
Jackson 402 sent $20.
Praise be to Jesus.
Praise be to Louis and pray for Cody Wilson.
Is that that guy that made those like a 3D printer?
of our 108s and 20 hours worship the creator not the creation Jews not chief. We worshiping
a calf Jesus worship the creator not the creation Christians not chief. He would he would he would
worshiping you be quite way. I'm not even really following you to $6.50. Why don't you have a debate
with Mohammed hijab? It will be interesting thing. Then we will see how is the how is true.
I don't really think he has enough clout for that. I think he's sort of an ankle bider. Also,
theology is not what I do. I'm not a theological debater. I'm a political live streamer. So these
people they always want to go have a theological debate. And it's like you literally do theological
debates for a living. That is what you do. All you do is debate religion every day, giving
dialogue, debating these things. And it's like a debate bro thing. So, you know, politics is what
I do. My my conviction is I don't want Muslims in America. If you want a debate about that,
I'll debate that. I have not read the Quran. I'm not a Muslim. I don't know Muslim theology.
Not very well. I know some of it. So if I were to do a theological debate, I would need to
prepare for an extended period of time because theology is a huge. It involves historicity and
involves philosophy. It involves a lot of things and you want to be prepared. So if I did a
Muslim debate, I would want to hire profile opponent. And I would need some time. If you want to
debate about Muslims, I mean, maybe I would do a 2v2 with sneakers, maybe something like that.
And it would be about politics because I'm not here to say, um, you know, I'm not even saying you
can't be Muslim. You want to be Muslim, knock yourself out. I don't care. But the question is,
is America a Christian country? Should we have these people coming here by the millions? And I
think the answer is no. Then they want to make it about, well, we, I want to trap you into a semantic
debate. And I'm not interested in that. McKenzie, you said $20. Did you get a haircut recently?
You've been looking so good this week. Thanks. Really? You mean it? Yeah, I got a little haircut.
It's really nothing. Thanks. Thank you. I appreciate that. Yeah, I got to hear a cut last week.
Open door 1235 cent $20. Tell me why I'm stuck as a virgin with rage. Tell me why I want a cute girl
my age. Tell me why I never want to hear you say I have a boyfriend, Christian, Weston Chandler.
Is that really that he said at the end $36 and $50 the gear you act with the bros, the straighter you are.
You know, I think that is generally true. However, I think that is true up until a point, you know,
because that was wild. That wasn't like that wasn't like a hey, we're being funny. That was like
it was just like a little hey, I'm not saying they're gay. I'm just saying it was like a yo pause. That's all.
America, they're sent $20. Will cozy ever be fixed? The streams and replays no longer work.
All right, he cozy if not. Is it broken? Listen, cozy is just a backup at this low IQ,
bro, I present $20 met six to five and when they're praised, they'll shout not be as the hypocrites are
for they love to praise standing in the synagogues and in the corners of the streets that they may be seeing
them up. Verly I say unto you, they have the reward. Perfect response for the Muslims in time
square. Take that sniko praying for you. W I Y tricks sent $25 a little birdie told me you
incline a front row seats to the elimination chamber in Chicago Saturday and are going to mug the whole
time. Speaking of WWE, see how punk is from Chicago and is posting about how I should leave Chicago.
ESPN owns the rights now in Netflix broadcasted worldwide. So you incline being there will be peak.
I don't know who told you that. Just pop gesture sent $25. What is your proposition to dealing with
African Americans policy wise? I genuinely don't enjoy being around them. But do you think we can
co-exist or does the abridious behavior make it impossible? Yeah, we can co-exist. We just need to
arrest all of the worst ones because the look, black people are being obnoxious. That's one thing.
People would be it would be less problematic if they weren't committing all this violent crime.
That's priority number one. So we got to get control of the public transit, the cities,
get the crime down. And then, you know, we should just encourage a culture of
consideration and respect and manners and people should be shamed and maybe even arrested if
they don't do that. Randy exp's sent $20. Thank you for your service, sir. I hope you run for
president and we're all fortunate enough to see a new America under your movement. You've changed
my life and I appreciate you. 31-year-old from CA. Thank you, man. I appreciate you.
People take sent $50. Love from Georgia. God bless. Thanks. Here at Notice sent $20. Wait until
Muslims wake up to the fact their religion was invented by the Jews to counter the rays of Christianity.
But they're not ready for that. They sent $20. Hey, I like La La land in the notebook.
I never saw the notebook. G agent seven sent $20. Knock down, drag out.
That's what I was thinking. Low IQ broider sent $20. I went down to Black Cube,
but whole after watching your recent clip about it. Is it ironic that when you unfold the cube,
it turns into a cross. So the Jews and the Muslims are low-key worshiping Christ,
deli of Jesus. Yeah, I don't know. That's the street.
HC grow-yper sent $20. Free Miniga. Griffin fullers sent $20. Fuck-nickers.
Okay. Play gruy sent $20. I love how like half of Huckers DC and merch features quotes from
your interview. Do you get a cut of the sales? Yeah, I can't believe that's still up. I don't,
I haven't seen that. Not for sure for sent $20. Why do you want grow-yper's to clean the
goat shit off sneakers? Dick for him. He's your Fortnite duo. Not ours.
Okay, that's crazy. I don't think anything has said that. I'm a baby gruyper. Where's mom sucky-sucky-sucky-milky-milky?
Okay, Peterson sent $20. My dad died today. Can I get a hat for his memory?
He was a wang if we watched you every day. He had leukemia, skeptical thanks for everything you
do Christ's kings. Merch will help. Okay, that's crazy. That's actually all about your
$20. Nick, have you ever tried Carnita's Don Alfredo and Stone Park? It's really good
in their opening a new location on Oregon in Brookfield. Worth a visit.
No, I haven't. I know where that is. I know exactly where Stone Park is. My go-to over there is
a Totonilco, which is right there. But no, I've never- I've seen it. I drive by it all the time.
When you go to the airport, when you're on manheim, right? I think that's where it is, right? Maybe I'm
tripping, but yeah, yeah. No, I've never been there. That's not my spot.
Mosher Goldberg sent $20. Any opinion on the SSPX? They will consecrate new bishops. The Vatican
doesn't want to allow it. Might be a schism. I saw that. Yeah, I don't approve. I think it's-
I've always said they're tending towards schism. And people said they're not schismatic.
They're in communion. And I said, yeah, but they're tending towards schism.
And look at what happened. So I've never been a huge fan. I mean, in theory, I like what they
represent, but it's too ideological. It's too divisive. Okay. All right. That's our last
super chat. That's going to do it for me. Remember, as always, to smash the follow button, smash the
like button, leave a comment. Let me know what you think about the show. Check out the merch store.
Fuentes not store. I'm on the air money through Friday. As always, thank you to our top super
chatters. Special thanks to Sage Blair, Nigel Soar. I think that's from yesterday.
Nigel Soar is yeah, bears big, but dinky DS, just a girl Brent Peterson, Zionism and Francesco.
Big thanks to them. Thanks to all our super chatters, everybody. The watches we love you.
I'll see you tomorrow until then have a great rest of your evening.
With respect, to respect that we deserve.
From this day, all this is going to be only America first. America first.
You